<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en-US">
  <title>Judy Winsor — Journal</title>
  <id>https://journal.judywinsor.com</id>
  <updated>2025-09-22T00:00:00Z</updated>
  <generator>Eleventy</generator>

  <!-- self + site links -->
  <link rel="self" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com/feed.atom" type="application/atom+xml" />
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com" type="text/html" />

  
  <entry>
    <title>September 22, 2025</title>

    <!-- canonical id + link -->
    <id>https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/09/22/</id>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/09/22/" type="text/html" />

    <!-- dates -->
    <updated>2025-09-22T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2025-09-22T00:00:00Z</published>

    <!-- author -->
    <author><name>Judy Winsor</name></author>

    <!-- tags -->
    
      
        <category term="#fall" />
      
        <category term="#compliments" />
      
        <category term="#gratitude" />
      
    

    <!-- full HTML content -->
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <h2>Tasks</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] Mail orders</li>
<li>[x] Work day</li>
<li>[x] Refill Rx</li>
</ul>
<h2>Sleep</h2>
<ul>
<li>8 hr 9 min — 82% good</li>
</ul>
<h2>Habits</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] am meds</li>
<li>[x] planner fill</li>
<li>[ ] self care</li>
<li>[x] shop orders</li>
<li>[x] noon meds</li>
<li>[x] no spend</li>
<li>[x] CM &amp; H logs</li>
<li>[x] yoga/movement</li>
</ul>
<h2>Word</h2>
<p><strong>Catch-22</strong> <em>(noun)</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Refers to a difficult situation for which there is no easy or possible solution.</li>
<li>A problematic situation for which the only solution is denied by a circumstance inherent in the problem or by a rule.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p><em>I’m in a Catch-22: to get the job I need experience, but how do I get experience if I can’t get the job?</em></p>
</blockquote>
<h2>Journal</h2>
<p>Happy September Equinox!<br>
Fall starts today but our weather hasn’t gotten the memo. I have 6 orders to fill today—woot woot. I got bit by a fall fashion shopping bug last night. It always happens around my birthday because it’s the only season I really enjoy shopping for clothes. Sweaters and jackets! Boots and bags! Summer is the worst—I always feel too exposed and when it’s humid I just want to wear whatever absorbs sweat the best LOL.</p>
<h2>Prompt</h2>
<p><strong>Prompt 22: What’s a recent comment or message that made you smile?</strong><br>
I was at work last week lugging buckets of water around—being grumpy about it. And someone saw me and said “I like your hair!” It snapped me totally out of it and made me smile. It felt really genuine. Ever since I switched to my natural waves a year or two ago, no one really comments anymore (which makes sense because it doesn’t change). But it was nice to hear from a stranger and broke my stormy mood for the moment.</p>
<p>I wish I was better about complimenting other people. I get scared I’ll get stuck in a whole awkward conversation if I open the door so I always chicken out unless I know someone really well already. Introverting is hard like that. I never know when to push myself out of my comfort zone. Will I regret it, or will it be a kind/awesome thing?</p>
<hr>
<h2>📌 Summary</h2>
<ul>
<li>✅ <strong>Great sleep</strong> (8+ hours)</li>
<li>⚠️ <strong>Missed habits</strong>: self care</li>
<li>✅ <strong>All tasks completed</strong></li>
<li>✨ <strong>Mood</strong>: reflective and uplifted</li>
<li>🏷️ <strong>Tags</strong>: #fall #compliments #gratitude</li>
</ul>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>September 21, 2025</title>

    <!-- canonical id + link -->
    <id>https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/09/21/</id>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/09/21/" type="text/html" />

    <!-- dates -->
    <updated>2025-09-21T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2025-09-21T00:00:00Z</published>

    <!-- author -->
    <author><name>Judy Winsor</name></author>

    <!-- tags -->
    
      
        <category term="#smallbusiness" />
      
        <category term="#reflection" />
      
        <category term="#rainyday" />
      
    

    <!-- full HTML content -->
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <h2>Tasks</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] Refill pillboxes</li>
<li>[x] Trash day</li>
<li>[x] Bath</li>
<li>[x] Weekly planning</li>
</ul>
<h2>Sleep</h2>
<ul>
<li>8 hr 43 min — 88% good</li>
</ul>
<h2>Habits</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] Am meds</li>
<li>[x] Planner fill</li>
<li>[x] Self care</li>
<li>[x] Shop orders</li>
<li>[x] Noon meds</li>
<li>[x] No spend</li>
<li>[x] CM + H logs</li>
<li>[ ] Yoga/movement</li>
</ul>
<h2>Word</h2>
<p><strong>lugubrious</strong> <em>(adj.)</em></p>
<ul>
<li>A formal word used chiefly to describe something that is very sad especially in an exaggerated or insincere way.</li>
<li>Can also describe something that shows or expresses gloom.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p><em>The movie’s stunning cinematography could not make up for the lugubrious and plodding plot.</em><br>
<em>The lugubrious mood of the room shifted when the voices of children playing erupted outside the window.</em></p>
</blockquote>
<h2>Journal</h2>
<p>It’s the last official day of summer! I’m ready for it to go. It was a very slow morning. No reason but I was just sleepy and cozy in bed. I’ve been working hard lately so I’m saying it’s okay if today is just chill.</p>
<p>Last night my brain rapidly melted down. Not 100%, but borderline existential crisis mode. I just have an order that went missing but it was marked delivered. So I can’t file an insurance claim or even a missing mail search. It just makes me sad that I can’t control the entire process and it costs me—despite doing all the “right” things to protect my orders.</p>
<p>So I was just questioning my life decision to run my own business and all the stress that means for me. I just wonder sometimes if working for someone else would make me feel more secure. Ultimately I still believe my shop is absolutely the best choice for me, but there are doubts. And I don’t have any business partner to talk me through it so I need to give myself the pep talk.</p>
<p>The grind is a real thing and stickers are a brutal business. The amount of SKUs required to stay relevant is a bit wild for one person. And maybe it never makes any profit. At least people are connecting with my art. That’s a rare and special thing!</p>
<h2>📌 Summary</h2>
<ul>
<li>✅ <strong>Great sleep</strong> (8h 43m)</li>
<li>⚠️ <strong>Missed habits</strong>: yoga/movement</li>
<li>✅ <strong>All tasks completed</strong></li>
<li>✨ <strong>Mood</strong>: reflective, slightly overwhelmed</li>
<li>🏷️ <strong>Tags</strong>: #smallbusiness #reflection #rainyday</li>
</ul>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>September 20, 2025</title>

    <!-- canonical id + link -->
    <id>https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/09/20/</id>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/09/20/" type="text/html" />

    <!-- dates -->
    <updated>2025-09-20T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2025-09-20T00:00:00Z</published>

    <!-- author -->
    <author><name>Judy Winsor</name></author>

    <!-- tags -->
    
      
        <category term="#planner" />
      
        <category term="#smallbusiness" />
      
        <category term="#creativity" />
      
    

    <!-- full HTML content -->
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <h2>Tasks</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] Laundry</li>
<li>[x] Mail order</li>
<li>[x] S.M. Post</li>
</ul>
<h2>Sleep</h2>
<ul>
<li>7 hr 51 min, 75% fair</li>
</ul>
<h2>Habits</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] am meds</li>
<li>[x] planner fill</li>
<li>[x] self care</li>
<li>[x] shop orders</li>
<li>[x] noon meds</li>
<li>[x] no spend</li>
<li>[x] CM + H logs</li>
<li>[ ] yoga/movement</li>
</ul>
<h2>Word</h2>
<p><strong>enmity</strong> <em>(noun)</em></p>
<ul>
<li>a formal word that refers to a very deep unfriendly feeling, such as hatred or ill will, that is often felt mutually.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>Having to collaborate on the project only increased the bitterness and enmity between the two coworkers, who had never gotten along.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2>Journal</h2>
<p>Not sure why but my stomach woke me up at 5:30am and I did not feel well at all. Yuck! I eventually got back to sleep but it was not a fun night. I feel fine now! We ate a nice HelloFresh dinner with pork and spaghetti. IDK if maybe that was it? I never really know.</p>
<p>I spent all day yesterday working on coloring my new Cousin sticker kit. I'm always spinning my wheels with color. I don't like for it to look too simple or garish but I also don't know when to stop either. I do my best! I need to make the little art deco for the boxes and then the art is mostly done.</p>
<p>Later... spent the day finalizing my new kit and did a test print-and-cut (it looks good!). I am mentally exhausted at the idea of writing a listing though, so maybe I should take it easy. The burnout is feeling super tangible right now. I really don't know how anyone runs a sticker shop successfully, all on their own. I am wiped out. Phew!</p>
<h2>Prompt</h2>
<p><strong>Prompt 20: What trend have you seen lately that you're tempted to try?</strong><br>
I'm pretty out of the loop on trends. I mostly consume &quot;planner&quot; content on social media. I have been wanting to use my Traveler's Notebook more even though I do zero traveling. Just as another journal. That's not really a trend though. I'm just super focused on shop work right now.</p>
<h2>📌 Summary</h2>
<ul>
<li>⚠️ <strong>Short sleep</strong> (under 8h15m)</li>
<li>⚠️ <strong>Missed habits</strong>: yoga/movement</li>
<li>✅ <strong>All tasks completed</strong></li>
<li>✨ <strong>Mood</strong>: exhausted but accomplished</li>
<li>🏷️ <strong>Tags</strong>: #planner #smallbusiness #creativity</li>
</ul>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>September 19, 2025</title>

    <!-- canonical id + link -->
    <id>https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/09/19/</id>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/09/19/" type="text/html" />

    <!-- dates -->
    <updated>2025-09-19T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2025-09-19T00:00:00Z</published>

    <!-- author -->
    <author><name>Judy Winsor</name></author>

    <!-- tags -->
    
      
        <category term="#overwhelm" />
      
        <category term="#smallbiz" />
      
        <category term="#reflection" />
      
    

    <!-- full HTML content -->
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <h2>Tasks</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] Mail orders</li>
<li>[x] Bath</li>
<li>[x] Design day</li>
</ul>
<h2>Sleep</h2>
<ul>
<li>9 hr 10 min — 85% good</li>
</ul>
<h2>Habits</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] Am meds</li>
<li>[x] Planner fill</li>
<li>[x] Self care</li>
<li>[x] Shop orders</li>
<li>[x] Noon meds</li>
<li>[x] No spend</li>
<li>[x] CM+ H logs</li>
<li>[ ] Yoga/movement</li>
</ul>
<h2>Word</h2>
<p><strong>succumb</strong> <em>(verb)</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Someone who succumbs to a pressure or emotion stops trying to resist that pressure or emotion</li>
<li>Someone who succumbs to an injury or disease dies because of it</li>
<li>Yielding to something</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>The program aims to help kids develop the strength of character required to avoid succumbing to peer pressure.<br>
Many patients diagnosed with the disease live healthy lives for years before succumbing to it.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2>Journal</h2>
<p>Hello Friday! Work was kind of a bummer yesterday. I don’t have room for anything so it’s not satisfying to finish up. It’s just technically “done” but not good in my eyes. It’s becoming very disheartening and I dunno how to turn my attitude about it around. It’s also just physically exhausting every single time. I think the satisfaction of having done a good job used to push me through. Now I just barely survive. And now I need to pivot to my shop today even though I’d love to just rest and recover. What’s that saying? Burning the candle at both ends. Yeah. That’s me lately.</p>
<h2>Prompt</h2>
<p><strong>Prompt 19: What’s a sound, flavor, or texture that grounds you?</strong><br>
I’ve come to really love white noise. Always helps me fall asleep now. Even at work if there’s a heavy downpour of rain it sounds like white noise and it’s like I can breathe again. Ice cold water can be similar. Refreshing and like a little reset button on the senses. A strong cool breeze. Haha maybe if I just lived near a mountain waterfall I’d be grounded all the time?</p>
<h2>📌 Summary</h2>
<ul>
<li>✅ <strong>Great sleep</strong> (9 hr 10 min)</li>
<li>⚠️ <strong>Missed habits</strong>: yoga/movement</li>
<li>✅ <strong>All tasks completed</strong></li>
<li>✨ <strong>Mood</strong>: overwhelmed and drained</li>
<li>🏷️ <strong>Tags</strong>: #overwhelm #smallbiz #reflection</li>
</ul>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>September 18, 2025</title>

    <!-- canonical id + link -->
    <id>https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/09/18/</id>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/09/18/" type="text/html" />

    <!-- dates -->
    <updated>2025-09-18T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2025-09-18T00:00:00Z</published>

    <!-- author -->
    <author><name>Judy Winsor</name></author>

    <!-- tags -->
    
      
        <category term="#sticker_design" />
      
        <category term="#planning" />
      
        <category term="#weather" />
      
    

    <!-- full HTML content -->
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <h2>Tasks</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] Work day</li>
<li>[x] Mail order</li>
</ul>
<h2>Sleep</h2>
<ul>
<li>8 hr 3 min — 77% fair</li>
</ul>
<h2>Habits</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] am meds</li>
<li>[x] planner fill</li>
<li>[ ] self care</li>
<li>[x] shop orders</li>
<li>[x] noon meds</li>
<li>[x] no spend</li>
<li>[x] CM + H logs</li>
<li>[x] yoga/movement</li>
</ul>
<h2>Word</h2>
<p><strong>rationale</strong> <em>(noun)</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Refers to an explanation or reason for something said or done. It is often used with <em>for</em>, <em>behind</em>, or <em>of</em>.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>City council members who oppose the zoning change should be ready to explain their rationale for voting against it.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2>Journal</h2>
<p>I spent all of yesterday designing a new sticker kit. I’m still finishing up the coloring portion. It has some really beautiful scenes but maybe a tiny bit too much detail? Idk, maybe just the right amount. It’s got strong winter vibes so I can’t procrastinate on this one! I’m excited to use it myself.</p>
<p>My troubled TikTok package finally got scanned into the system in Florida of all places. No place to scan it between Wisconsin and Florida?! At least it’s finally in there.</p>
<p>They should be finishing up the pavement repairs today but my van is parked one street over so I’ll have to walk a little to get to it. I repeat: Summer go away, you are no longer welcome here. I want fall!</p>
<p>This ink is too light on this paper.</p>
<h2>Prompt</h2>
<p><strong>Prompt 8: What is your current favorite little luxury?</strong><br>
The thing I splurge on most often is stickers. It’s a small thing that is just designed to make planning and journaling more fun. I get to find visuals that match my inner feelings.<br>
It really has helped so much in the past year too that I’ve been consistently journaling. I know my ADHD brain would get bored if it was all text and no fun art. I am so much more organized in my thoughts now. But yes it is a luxury because it’s not required for living—just really nice to have.</p>
<h2>📌 Summary</h2>
<ul>
<li>⚠️ <strong>Short sleep</strong> (just over 8 hours but not fully restful)</li>
<li>⚠️ <strong>Missed habits</strong>: self care</li>
<li>✅ <strong>All tasks completed</strong></li>
<li>✨ <strong>Mood</strong>: productive but longing for fall</li>
<li>🏷️ <strong>Tags</strong>: #sticker_design #planning #weather</li>
</ul>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>September 17, 2025</title>

    <!-- canonical id + link -->
    <id>https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/09/17/</id>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/09/17/" type="text/html" />

    <!-- dates -->
    <updated>2025-09-17T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2025-09-17T00:00:00Z</published>

    <!-- author -->
    <author><name>Judy Winsor</name></author>

    <!-- tags -->
    
      
        <category term="#fountainpens" />
      
        <category term="#shopwork" />
      
        <category term="#stationery" />
      
    

    <!-- full HTML content -->
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <h2>Tasks</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] bath</li>
<li>[x] move van</li>
<li>[x] HF delivery</li>
</ul>
<h2>Sleep</h2>
<ul>
<li>8 hr 45 min — 90% excellent</li>
</ul>
<h2>Habits</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] planner fill</li>
<li>[x] am meds</li>
<li>[x] self care</li>
<li>[x] shop orders</li>
<li>[x] noon meds</li>
<li>[x] no spend</li>
<li>[x] CM + H logs</li>
<li>[ ] yoga/movement</li>
</ul>
<h2>Word</h2>
<p><strong>jovial</strong> <em>(adjective)</em></p>
<ul>
<li>describes people as well as moods, attitudes, etc.; that are cheerful and jolly.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>The audience was in a jovial mood as the headlining comedian walked onto the stage.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2>Journal</h2>
<p>Not sure if this ink is dark enough to be considered easily legible but I filled my new pen with it, so we’re stuck for awhile. My final order from Boston General Store arrived yesterday and I got myself a treat: a TWSBI Eco with a fine nib in Espresso Bronze. It’s very pretty! And now I’m all set with my planners for 2026.</p>
<p>Today they are sealing cracks in the pavement so I had to move my van to a different street. I used to have divots in the pavement where I always parked but they filled those in yesterday.</p>
<p>I think I’ll do some design work for the shop today since I’m basically stuck at home. I think I should make another weekly kit. It would be nice to have more than 2 in the shop. But they take awhile so IDK how far I’ll get today.</p>
<h2>Prompt</h2>
<p><strong>If you had a shop mascot, what would it be and what would they do all day?</strong><br>
Well I guess this question only makes sense for shop owners. Maybe a chicken? Running around all day, feeling scattered and overwhelmed, haha. At least lately. I feel pulled in a million directions but I’m spending my time wisely... but also, I do have Cookie, my actual shop mascot. A chocolate chip cookie with a bite taken out. Sweet but has been through some stuff. Also a good analogy for myself at times!</p>
<hr>
<h2>📌 Summary</h2>
<ul>
<li>✅ <strong>Great sleep</strong> (8h 45m)</li>
<li>⚠️ <strong>Missed habits</strong>: yoga/movement</li>
<li>✅ <strong>All tasks completed</strong></li>
<li>✨ <strong>Mood</strong>: cheerful but uncertain</li>
<li>🏷️ <strong>Tags</strong>: #fountainpens #shopwork #stationery</li>
</ul>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>September 16, 2025</title>

    <!-- canonical id + link -->
    <id>https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/09/16/</id>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/09/16/" type="text/html" />

    <!-- dates -->
    <updated>2025-09-16T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2025-09-16T00:00:00Z</published>

    <!-- author -->
    <author><name>Judy Winsor</name></author>

    <!-- tags -->
    
      
        <category term="#therapy" />
      
        <category term="#tiktokshop" />
      
        <category term="#fountainpens" />
      
    

    <!-- full HTML content -->
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <h2>Tasks</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] appt. 3 pm → 1 pm</li>
<li>[x] clean fountain pen</li>
<li>[x] ink TWSBI fine FP</li>
</ul>
<h2>Sleep</h2>
<ul>
<li>8 hr 24 min — 86% good</li>
</ul>
<h2>Habits</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] am meds</li>
<li>[x] planner fill</li>
<li>[x] self care</li>
<li>[x] shop orders</li>
<li>[x] noon meds</li>
<li>[ ] no spend</li>
<li>[x] cm + h logs</li>
<li>[ ] yoga/movement</li>
</ul>
<h2>Word</h2>
<p><strong>debunk</strong> <em>(verb)</em></p>
<ul>
<li>To debunk something (such as a belief or theory) is to show that it is not true.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>The influencer remained enormously popular despite having the bulk of their health claims thoroughly debunked.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2>Journal</h2>
<p>Wow I should NOT have had that hot dog for dinner last night. Tummy troubles for real! Ugh. Was also just wiped after work yesterday so it was a double whammy. Hopefully today isn’t nearly so exhausting. But also why is it the middle of summer heat again? I’ve seen leaves changing on trees—this can’t happen. I do NOT approve. Our fall preview was so beautiful and lovely.</p>
<p>Anyways—I have nothing but trouble with my TikTok Shop. Everything had been fine for a few months but now my local post office is back to not scanning my outgoing packages so the system thinks I’m not sending things out when I 100% am. I’ll have to walk in and get a receipt for every package again. Super annoying and time consuming. You never know how slow the line will be. Why don’t they just scan all mail from the mailboxes? I do not get it at all.</p>
<h2>Prompt</h2>
<p><strong>Prompt 16: What’s your personal definition of “productive” right now?</strong><br>
Probably not a very balanced idea of it right now. I feel like I want to be designing new sticker sheets everyday and keeping up with production and orders and social media all at the same time. Conceptually I understand that it’s productive to rest and rejuvenate but I don’t always allow that reality. It should be just that I try each day and do what I can.</p>
<hr>
<h2>📌 Summary</h2>
<ul>
<li>✅ <strong>Great sleep</strong> (8 hr 24 min)</li>
<li>⚠️ <strong>Missed habits</strong>: no spend, yoga/movement</li>
<li>✅ <strong>All tasks completed</strong></li>
<li>✨ <strong>Mood</strong>: exhausted and frustrated</li>
<li>🏷️ <strong>Tags</strong>: #therapy #tiktokshop #fountainpens</li>
</ul>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>September 15, 2025</title>

    <!-- canonical id + link -->
    <id>https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/09/15/</id>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/09/15/" type="text/html" />

    <!-- dates -->
    <updated>2025-09-15T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2025-09-15T00:00:00Z</published>

    <!-- author -->
    <author><name>Judy Winsor</name></author>

    <!-- tags -->
    
      
        <category term="#work" />
      
        <category term="#shop" />
      
        <category term="#reflection" />
      
    

    <!-- full HTML content -->
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <h2>Tasks</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] Work day</li>
<li>[x] Mail order</li>
<li>[x] Refill g.l.c.</li>
<li>[x] Groceries</li>
</ul>
<h2>Sleep</h2>
<ul>
<li>8 hr 48 min — 86% good</li>
</ul>
<h2>Habits</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] Am meds</li>
<li>[x] Planner fill</li>
<li>[ ] Self care</li>
<li>[x] Shop orders</li>
<li>[x] Noon meds</li>
<li>[x] No spend</li>
<li>[x] Cm + H logs</li>
<li>[x] Yoga/movement</li>
</ul>
<h2>Word</h2>
<p><strong>askance</strong> <em>(adverb)</em></p>
<ul>
<li>in a way that shows a lack of trust or approval</li>
<li>with a side glance</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p><em>I couldn’t help but look askance at the dealer’s assurances that the car hadn’t ever been in an accident.</em><br>
<em>Several people eyed them askance when they walked into the room.</em></p>
</blockquote>
<h2>Journal</h2>
<p>It’s a new week. I took Saturday and Sunday off from shop stuff. I’m feeling more fresh mentally but I am a little worried I broke my momentum. I only have one order to mail today. Maybe it’s unrelated but who knows! I need to pick up some groceries after work today. It should be a normal day, nothing exciting in the forecast.</p>
<p>Although my order from Boston General Store might arrive. It said last Friday but it got delayed so now it says today. There’s no rush but it would be nice to “complete” my 2026 Hobonichi haul.</p>
<h2>Prompt</h2>
<p><strong>Prompt 15: What seasonal trend are you irrationally excited (or annoyed) about?</strong><br>
Maybe this makes me a cranky old person but I’m not into trick or treating. I don’t want to hand out candy to a bunch of strangers who come to my house. I enjoyed doing it as a kid — trick or treating — but the adult portion is not fun for me. It’s probably because I’m a bit of a hermit, and my home is my sanctuary away from the world of people. It’s just not my thing. M. always hands out the candy anyway. I’ll just put out the candy bowl if I ever have to one day. Sorry kids, I’d rather be you!</p>
<h2>📌 Summary</h2>
<ul>
<li>✅ <strong>Great sleep</strong> (8 hr 48 min)</li>
<li>⚠️ <strong>Missed habits</strong>: self care</li>
<li>✅ <strong>All tasks completed</strong></li>
<li>✨ <strong>Mood</strong>: reflective, mildly anxious</li>
<li>🏷️ <strong>Tags</strong>: #work #shop #reflection</li>
</ul>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>September 14, 2025</title>

    <!-- canonical id + link -->
    <id>https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/09/14/</id>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/09/14/" type="text/html" />

    <!-- dates -->
    <updated>2025-09-14T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2025-09-14T00:00:00Z</published>

    <!-- author -->
    <author><name>Judy Winsor</name></author>

    <!-- tags -->
    
      
        <category term="#weekly_reset" />
      
        <category term="#cozy_games" />
      
        <category term="#self_care" />
      
    

    <!-- full HTML content -->
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <h2>Tasks</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] Refill pillboxes</li>
<li>[x] Weekly planning</li>
<li>[x] Trash day</li>
<li>[x] Bath</li>
</ul>
<h2>Sleep</h2>
<ul>
<li>8 hr 42 min — 86% good</li>
</ul>
<h2>Habits</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] am meds</li>
<li>[x] planner fill</li>
<li>[x] self care</li>
<li>[x] shop orders</li>
<li>[x] noon meds</li>
<li>[x] no spend</li>
<li>[x] CM + H logs</li>
<li>[ ] yoga/movement</li>
</ul>
<h2>Word</h2>
<p><strong>Perpetuity</strong> <em>(noun)</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Refers to a state of continuing forever or for a very long time.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>The property will be passed on from generation to generation in perpetuity.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2>Journal</h2>
<p>Taking care of all the routine weekly chores today. I decided to take yesterday off from work.</p>
<p>Played a game on my Switch called <em>Escape from Mystwood Mansion</em>. I finished it—but forgot one thing so it was totally unsatisfying. Whoops! Also all the puzzles felt inconsistent—did 75% of them were fine but the others were too hard or just super complicated. It just felt like not the most professionally made game. Could have used more testing I think. 3.5 of 5 stars.</p>
<p>It was a nice change of pace from all the work though. Hopefully my brain appreciated the break!</p>
<h2>Prompt</h2>
<p><strong>Prompt 14: What's something cozy you wish was socially acceptable year-round?</strong><br>
It’s not unacceptable but hoodies and hot chocolate. Those things just don’t mesh well with summer heat. But both are cozy vibes! It might be less special and cozy if it was done all year round though. I do kind of wish I was one of those people who’s cold all the time so I could wear hoodies and sweaters all year long—but I’m the opposite.</p>
<hr>
<h2>📌 Summary</h2>
<ul>
<li>✅ <strong>Great sleep</strong> (8h42m)</li>
<li>⚠️ <strong>Missed habits</strong>: yoga/movement</li>
<li>✅ <strong>All tasks completed</strong></li>
<li>✨ <strong>Mood</strong>: balanced but slightly critical</li>
<li>🏷️ <strong>Tags</strong>: #weekly_reset #cozy_games #self_care</li>
</ul>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>September 13, 2025</title>

    <!-- canonical id + link -->
    <id>https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/09/13/</id>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/09/13/" type="text/html" />

    <!-- dates -->
    <updated>2025-09-13T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2025-09-13T00:00:00Z</published>

    <!-- author -->
    <author><name>Judy Winsor</name></author>

    <!-- tags -->
    
      
        <category term="#donuts" />
      
        <category term="#the_lazarus_project" />
      
        <category term="#sticker_shop" />
      
    

    <!-- full HTML content -->
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <h2>Tasks</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] Laundry</li>
<li>[x] Mail orders</li>
</ul>
<h2>Sleep</h2>
<ul>
<li>8 hr 18 min — 75% fair</li>
</ul>
<h2>Habits</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] am meds</li>
<li>[x] planner fill</li>
<li>[x] self care</li>
<li>[x] shop orders</li>
<li>[x] noon meds</li>
<li>[x] no spend</li>
<li>[x] CM + H logs</li>
<li>[ ] yoga/movement</li>
</ul>
<h2>Word</h2>
<p><strong>Consummate</strong> <em>(adj)</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Someone or something described as consummate is very skilled or accomplished.</li>
<li>Of the highest degree.</li>
<li>Complete in every detail.</li>
<li>Always used before the noun it describes.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p><em>Ever the consummate professional, the planner was sure that no one attending the event was aware of all the elements that had not gone as planned.</em></p>
</blockquote>
<h2>Journal</h2>
<p>M. got me donuts for breakfast! Yummy! Haven’t done that in forever. I finished watching season 2 of <em>The Lazarus Project</em> last night. It’s a good show. If there is another season, I know I’m going to have to rewatch this one though. Time travel makes for a confusing plot!</p>
<p>Yesterday was very productive, so I don’t know what I should do today. More work? Or more chill? I’m not very good at gauging how much energy I’m going to have on any given day. I guess I just fly by the seat of my pants most days.</p>
<p>I think I’ve already released 4 new sticker sheets just this month so far. Maybe it should be an “off” day to recharge.</p>
<h2>Prompt</h2>
<p><strong>Prompt 13: What household chore do you secretly enjoy more than you admit?</strong><br>
Not sure it’s a secret but laundry! I love having my dresser and closet fully stocked at the end of the week. I feel more prepared for anything that might happen that week. Even if I have to do something last minute I can do it in my favorite jeans or whatever. It’s that small sense of control and a full reset for the new week.</p>
<hr>
<h2>📌 Summary</h2>
<ul>
<li>✅ <strong>Great sleep</strong> (8h18m)</li>
<li>⚠️ <strong>Missed habits</strong>: yoga/movement</li>
<li>✅ <strong>All tasks completed</strong></li>
<li>✨ <strong>Mood</strong>: reflective but productive</li>
<li>🏷️ <strong>Tags</strong>: #donuts #the_lazarus_project #sticker_shop</li>
</ul>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>September 12, 2025</title>

    <!-- canonical id + link -->
    <id>https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/09/12/</id>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/09/12/" type="text/html" />

    <!-- dates -->
    <updated>2025-09-12T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2025-09-12T00:00:00Z</published>

    <!-- author -->
    <author><name>Judy Winsor</name></author>

    <!-- tags -->
    
      
        <category term="#shop_update" />
      
        <category term="#puzzle" />
      
        <category term="#creative_flow" />
      
    

    <!-- full HTML content -->
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <h2>Tasks</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] Mail orders</li>
<li>[x] Restocking</li>
<li>[x] List Winter Floral Deco</li>
<li>[x] Bath</li>
</ul>
<h2>Sleep</h2>
<ul>
<li>8 hr 51 min, 87% good</li>
</ul>
<h2>Habits</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] Am meds</li>
<li>[x] Planner fill</li>
<li>[x] Self care</li>
<li>[x] Shop orders</li>
<li>[x] Noon meds</li>
<li>[x] No spend</li>
<li>[x] CM + H logs</li>
<li>[ ] Yoga/movement</li>
</ul>
<h2>Word</h2>
<p><strong>flummox</strong> <em>(verb)</em></p>
<ul>
<li>To flummox someone is to confuse or perplex them.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>The actor was easily flummoxed by last-minute changes to the script.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2>Journal</h2>
<p>Hello Friday</p>
<p>Kind of an open day to do whatever I feel like. Not sure which tasks to prioritize today. I’ve been meaning to write a newsletter for the shop, I could do that. I could finalize a Deco sheet I started. Or I could start a totally new design. Hmm… not sure what would be best. Maybe finishing my deco sheet for a quick-ish win? It didn’t cut through last time and I have zero idea why. All the settings were the same as ever. New blade and pretty new sticky mat.</p>
<p>Oh I finished another jigsaw puzzle last night. I have 3 I’d like to glue together now. I just hate the smell of the glue so I also procrastinate that task. I think my 2nd part of my Hobonichi order should arrive today. Yay! I’ll have everything I need.</p>
<p>Later… worked on shop stuff. I figured out why my cuts were messed up—a tiny scrap of sticker paper got stuck to the blade. It was cutting most lines but not all the way. So I added a few imperfects/seconds for a discount to my Etsy. Then finished the Winter Floral deco and got it listed. Even got more inventory up to better levels and figured out my 2nd machine just needed a new cutting mat. So I was able to do a lot! Yay!</p>
<hr>
<h2>📌 Summary</h2>
<ul>
<li>✅ <strong>Great sleep</strong> (8 hr 51 min)</li>
<li>⚠️ <strong>Missed habits</strong>: yoga/movement</li>
<li>✅ <strong>All tasks completed</strong></li>
<li>✨ <strong>Mood</strong>: productive and light</li>
<li>🏷️ <strong>Tags</strong>: #shop_update #puzzle #creative_flow</li>
</ul>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>September 11, 2025</title>

    <!-- canonical id + link -->
    <id>https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/09/11/</id>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/09/11/" type="text/html" />

    <!-- dates -->
    <updated>2025-09-11T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2025-09-11T00:00:00Z</published>

    <!-- author -->
    <author><name>Judy Winsor</name></author>

    <!-- tags -->
    
      
        <category term="#work" />
      
        <category term="#balance" />
      
        <category term="#seasonal_snacks" />
      
    

    <!-- full HTML content -->
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <h2>Tasks</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] work</li>
<li>[x] mail orders</li>
<li>[x] s.m. post</li>
</ul>
<h2>Sleep</h2>
<ul>
<li>8 hr 40 min — 86% good</li>
</ul>
<h2>Habits</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] am meds</li>
<li>[x] planner fill</li>
<li>[x] self care</li>
<li>[x] shop orders</li>
<li>[x] noon meds</li>
<li>[x] no spend</li>
<li>[x] cm + h logs</li>
<li>[x] yoga/movement</li>
</ul>
<h2>Word</h2>
<p><strong>zoomorphic</strong> <em>(adj.)</em></p>
<ul>
<li>describes things that have the form of an animal</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>The local bakery is famous for its wide variety of zoomorphic treats, from “hedgehog” dinner rolls to delicate, swan-shaped pastries.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2>Journal</h2>
<p>Hello Thursday! It was nice to take a little break from shop work yesterday. I do need to remember to balance rejuvenation with hard work—even during busy seasons. It’s such a weird concept to feel pulled to do work but to not always follow through. Because in the end that’s the most sustainable path. I suppose with normal jobs where you work with and for other people you don’t get any choice. If they want to try to overwork you, they can. But there is also a “shared workload” to help offset some overwhelm.</p>
<p>It’s just an interesting gig being your own boss. And being a team of one person. I’m sure there isn’t one “right” way to do it. But I should enforce more balance when I can. Particularly with a creative/art business.</p>
<h2>Prompt</h2>
<p><strong>Prompt 11: What snack is wildly seasonal for you and why?</strong><br>
Very specifically a 3 Musketeers candy bar. It’s only for Halloween and literally no other time of the year. Maybe hot chocolate for winter, pumpkin pie for Thanksgiving. I think they’re just so seasonal because that’s when I first and subsequently had them the most. It’s not that they belong to specific times, it’s just too weird otherwise.</p>
<hr>
<h2>📌 Summary</h2>
<ul>
<li>✅ <strong>Great sleep</strong> (8 hr 40 min)</li>
<li>✅ <strong>All habits completed</strong></li>
<li>✅ <strong>All tasks completed</strong></li>
<li>✨ <strong>Mood</strong>: thoughtful about balance</li>
<li>🏷️ <strong>Tags</strong>: #work #balance #seasonal_snacks</li>
</ul>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>September 10, 2025</title>

    <!-- canonical id + link -->
    <id>https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/09/10/</id>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/09/10/" type="text/html" />

    <!-- dates -->
    <updated>2025-09-10T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2025-09-10T00:00:00Z</published>

    <!-- author -->
    <author><name>Judy Winsor</name></author>

    <!-- tags -->
    
      
        <category term="#hobonichi" />
      
        <category term="#beachday" />
      
        <category term="#happy_mail" />
      
    

    <!-- full HTML content -->
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <h2>Tasks</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] HF delivery</li>
<li>[x] mail order</li>
<li>[x] bath</li>
<li>[x] manicure</li>
</ul>
<h2>Sleep</h2>
<ul>
<li>8 hr 34 min — 87% good</li>
</ul>
<h2>Habits</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] am meds</li>
<li>[x] planner fill</li>
<li>[x] self care</li>
<li>[x] shop orders</li>
<li>[x] noon meds</li>
<li>[x] no spend</li>
<li>[x] cm + h logs</li>
<li>[x] yoga/movement</li>
</ul>
<h2>Word</h2>
<p><strong>griot</strong> <em>(noun)</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Refers to any of a class of musician-entertainers of Western Africa whose performances include tribal histories and genealogies.</li>
<li>Also used broadly to refer to a storyteller.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>Tracing her family lineage back to West African griots inspired the singer to focus on storytelling through her music.</p>
</blockquote>
<p><em>Note: I have never heard this word. Love one that is totally unfamiliar to me.</em></p>
<h2>Journal</h2>
<p><strong>free day</strong> — Time to choose how to spend it…</p>
<p>Options, options. I’m considering a beach day but I’m also on a roll with designing new products for the shop. Trying to avoid the dreaded burnout. Oh and my 2026 Hobonichi order from Atlas Stationers is out for delivery! Yay!</p>
<p>If it arrives soon I could film a lil haul for social media. Or set up pens in it… or stare at it! My other order isn’t supposed to arrive until Friday though. It’s just 3 items from the Tsuki no Iro collection (the index stickers, dot stickers, and add on sticky notes). But no way to know if it will be here soon or not.</p>
<p>I think I’ll do the beach—shop stuff always waits.</p>
<p>Later… The beach was cloudy and the waves were tiny so it felt very peaceful and quiet. Then when I got home my 2026 Hobonichi order had arrived! Yay! I have Wave Ave and Foggy Plaid Weeks for next year. Very happy to see them in person and know I’ll have them to use when the time comes.</p>
<h2>📌 Summary</h2>
<ul>
<li>✅ <strong>Great sleep</strong> (8 hr 34 min)</li>
<li>✅ <strong>All habits completed</strong></li>
<li>✅ <strong>All tasks completed</strong></li>
<li>✨ <strong>Mood</strong>: excited and peaceful</li>
<li>🏷️ <strong>Tags</strong>: #hobonichi #beachday #happy_mail</li>
</ul>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>September 9, 2025</title>

    <!-- canonical id + link -->
    <id>https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/09/09/</id>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/09/09/" type="text/html" />

    <!-- dates -->
    <updated>2025-09-09T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2025-09-09T00:00:00Z</published>

    <!-- author -->
    <author><name>Judy Winsor</name></author>

    <!-- tags -->
    
      
        <category term="#skincare" />
      
        <category term="#sensitive_skin" />
      
        <category term="#daily_log" />
      
    

    <!-- full HTML content -->
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <h2>Tasks</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] Mail orders</li>
<li>[x] Kristin 2pm</li>
</ul>
<h2>Sleep</h2>
<ul>
<li>9 hr 4 min, 87% good</li>
</ul>
<h2>Habits</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] am meds</li>
<li>[x] planner fill</li>
<li>[x] self care</li>
<li>[x] shop orders</li>
<li>[x] noon meds</li>
<li>[x] no spend</li>
<li>[x] CM + H logs</li>
<li>[ ] yoga/movement</li>
</ul>
<h2>Word</h2>
<p><strong>insinuate</strong> <em>(verb)</em></p>
<ul>
<li>To insinuate something (especially something bad or insulting) is to say it in a subtle or indirect way.</li>
<li>To gradually make (oneself) a part of a group, a person’s life, etc., often by behaving in a dishonest way.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>When the teacher questioned the students about their identical test answers, they knew she was insinuating that they had cheated.<br>
They have managed to insinuate themselves into the city’s most influential social circles.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2>Journal</h2>
<p>Hello Tuesday! I used my new face moisturizer last night and my skin is not happy. My face feels hurt today. I patch tested on my hand and no reaction. It might go away as my face gets used to it but I’m just grumpy they raised the price on my fave moisturizer sooo much. Us sensitive skin girlies can’t take the changes! I miss my old face wash by Eucerin too. I try my best to find similar ingredients but it’s hopeless. There’s just too many products to choose from! Maybe I should have looked for the cheap one from Trader Joe’s before buying the $25 stuff on Amazon. I don’t have the patience to do a Sephora sample run. Also it’s all pretty pricey there. This could all also be because of the changing humidity too… ugh.</p>
<h2>Prompt</h2>
<p><strong>Prompt 9: What’s something you hoard even though you barely use it?</strong><br>
Oof! Probably a few things. Computers probably. They cost so much when you buy them that it’s hard to let them go. Plus they have whole chunks of my life on them. And I love a random tech hobby every couple of years. Maybe shoes too. I love having the right pair for the exact weather/outfit. I’m always trying to balance my own comfort with style. Same with some of my clothes too. Probably because I’m very sensory sensitive.</p>
<h2>📌 Summary</h2>
<ul>
<li>✅ <strong>Great sleep</strong> (9 hr 4 min)</li>
<li>⚠️ <strong>Missed habits</strong>: yoga/movement</li>
<li>✅ <strong>All tasks completed</strong></li>
<li>✨ <strong>Mood</strong>: Grumpy about skincare changes</li>
<li>🏷️ <strong>Tags</strong>: #skincare #sensitive_skin #daily_log</li>
</ul>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title></title>

    <!-- canonical id + link -->
    <id>https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/09/08/</id>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/09/08/" type="text/html" />

    <!-- dates -->
    <updated>2025-09-08T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2025-09-08T00:00:00Z</published>

    <!-- author -->
    <author><name>Judy Winsor</name></author>

    <!-- tags -->
    

    <!-- full HTML content -->
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      
    ]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>September 7, 2025</title>

    <!-- canonical id + link -->
    <id>https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/09/07/</id>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/09/07/" type="text/html" />

    <!-- dates -->
    <updated>2025-09-07T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2025-09-07T00:00:00Z</published>

    <!-- author -->
    <author><name>Judy Winsor</name></author>

    <!-- tags -->
    
      
        <category term="#shop_updates" />
      
        <category term="#planner" />
      
        <category term="#reflection" />
      
    

    <!-- full HTML content -->
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <h2>Tasks</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] Refill pillboxes</li>
<li>[x] Trash day</li>
<li>[x] Weekly planning</li>
<li>[x] Bath</li>
<li>[x] Restock inventory</li>
</ul>
<h2>Sleep</h2>
<ul>
<li>8 hr 26 min — 86% good</li>
</ul>
<h2>Habits</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] Am meds</li>
<li>[x] Planner fill</li>
<li>[x] Self care</li>
<li>[x] Shop orders</li>
<li>[x] Noon meds</li>
<li>[x] No spend</li>
<li>[x] CM + H logs</li>
<li>[ ] Yoga/movement</li>
</ul>
<h2>Word</h2>
<p><strong>behest</strong> <em>(noun)</em></p>
<ul>
<li>An authoritative order</li>
<li>An urgent prompting</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>The committee met again at the senator’s behest.<br>
At the behest of her friends, Marnie read the poem aloud.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2>Journal</h2>
<p>Hello Sunday! Whoa I got a lot of new orders last night. I guess the algorithms like it when you add new products to the shop. I have 6 already and the day is young. I’ve seen some people already have their 2026 Hobonichi planners on social media. My order from Atlas Stationers still hasn’t been fulfilled but I know that their shipment arrived so they’re working on it.</p>
<p>Later… I spent the day filling orders and restocking sticker inventory. I maybe pushed it today with work because I tried to cut more after dinner but I screwed up the first few sheets. It’s frustrating how different my brain works in the evening. I wish I could get more done. I’m getting concerned about my ability to keep up this year. I don’t know if I’ll be able to or not.</p>
<h2>Prompt</h2>
<p><strong>Prompt 7: What weird or oddly specific smell makes you feel nostalgic?</strong><br>
Crayons or Elmer’s Glue. Instant childhood memories. That crayon wax smell is literally only crayons. Candle wax isn’t the same. A fresh box of crayons is just a highly specific thing for me. And yes I pronounce it like “cran”—sue me.</p>
<hr>
<h2>📌 Summary</h2>
<ul>
<li>✅ <strong>Great sleep</strong></li>
<li>⚠️ <strong>Missed habits</strong>: yoga/movement</li>
<li>✅ <strong>All tasks completed</strong></li>
<li>✨ <strong>Mood</strong>: Productive but mentally drained</li>
<li>🏷️ <strong>Tags</strong>: #shop_updates #planner #reflection</li>
</ul>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>September 6, 2025</title>

    <!-- canonical id + link -->
    <id>https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/09/06/</id>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/09/06/" type="text/html" />

    <!-- dates -->
    <updated>2025-09-06T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2025-09-06T00:00:00Z</published>

    <!-- author -->
    <author><name>Judy Winsor</name></author>

    <!-- tags -->
    
      
        <category term="#sticker_business" />
      
        <category term="#fall_vibes" />
      
        <category term="#creative_work" />
      
    

    <!-- full HTML content -->
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <h2>Tasks</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] Mail orders</li>
<li>[x] Laundry</li>
<li>[x] Buy moisturizer</li>
<li>[x] Thanksgiving listing</li>
<li>[x] S.m. post</li>
<li>[x] Christmas design and listing</li>
</ul>
<h2>Sleep</h2>
<ul>
<li>8 hr 22 min — 85% good</li>
</ul>
<h2>Habits</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] Am meds</li>
<li>[x] Planner fill</li>
<li>[x] Self care</li>
<li>[x] Shop orders</li>
<li>[x] Noon meds</li>
<li>[ ] No spend</li>
<li>[x] Cm + H logs</li>
<li>[ ] Yoga/movement</li>
</ul>
<h2>Word</h2>
<p><strong>mollify</strong> <em>(verb)</em></p>
<ul>
<li>to mollify someone is to make them less angry</li>
<li>can also mean to reduce in intensity</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>The celebrity’s statement was intended to mollify critics.<br>
Time mollified her anger.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2>Journal</h2>
<p>Hello Saturday! I have four orders to mail today. People are starting to buy their 2026 calendars so I think sticker season is beginning.</p>
<p>I refilled my printer ink for stickers yesterday, which is the first time I’ve had to do that since I got it. Good to know the ink lasts a long time. I want to write and photograph yesterday’s Thanksgiving sticker sheet so that’s totally done. I also need to re-ink this pen…  (Running out of ink!)</p>
<p>Christmas, Thanksgiving, and Halloween are all live now in the shop! Cookie’s collection is starting to feel a lot more complete. I’m so proud of myself for keeping up with an idea I believe in. My little Cookie character has had a bite taken out of them but they keep their spirits high!</p>
<p>I kind of want to make another zine now for Cookie to be featured in, but that’s not high on the seasonal importance list. Tomorrow will be either an off day for me or just restocking. Two sheets in two days from sketch to live is a LOT on my brain. Really, really happy to have some seasonal offerings this year though. Tired brain and all. Haha!</p>
<h2>📌 Summary</h2>
<ul>
<li>✅ <strong>Great sleep</strong> (8 hr 22 min)</li>
<li>⚠️ <strong>Missed habits</strong>: no spend, yoga/movement</li>
<li>✅ <strong>All tasks completed</strong></li>
<li>✨ <strong>Mood</strong>: productive but tired</li>
<li>🏷️ <strong>Tags</strong>: #sticker_business #fall_vibes #creative_work</li>
</ul>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>September 5, 2025</title>

    <!-- canonical id + link -->
    <id>https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/09/05/</id>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/09/05/" type="text/html" />

    <!-- dates -->
    <updated>2025-09-05T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2025-09-05T00:00:00Z</published>

    <!-- author -->
    <author><name>Judy Winsor</name></author>

    <!-- tags -->
    
      
        <category term="#shop" />
      
        <category term="#design" />
      
        <category term="#stickers" />
      
    

    <!-- full HTML content -->
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <h2>Tasks</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] mail order</li>
<li>[x] bath</li>
<li>[x] design day</li>
<li>[x] setup cable box</li>
</ul>
<h2>Sleep</h2>
<ul>
<li>8 hr 34 min, 85% good</li>
</ul>
<h2>Habits</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] am meds</li>
<li>[x] planner fill</li>
<li>[x] self care</li>
<li>[x] shop orders</li>
<li>[x] noon meds</li>
<li>[x] no spend</li>
<li>[x] CM + H logs</li>
<li>[ ] yoga/movement</li>
</ul>
<h2>Word</h2>
<p><strong>histrionic</strong> <em>(adj.)</em></p>
<ul>
<li>a word used disapprovingly to describe someone or something that is too emotional or dramatic</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>The head chef had a penchant for dish throwing, door slamming, and other histrionic displays of temper whenever a dish was sent back to the kitchen.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2>Journal</h2>
<p>Free day – what should I do?</p>
<p>Hello Friday! I’m torn between a long walk at the beach or a big design day for the shop. Good weather is so hard to come by but an entirely free day to dig in deep to design is  too! I’m leaning toward shop work day because I want to get seasonal stuff in the shop ASAP. I could always go out tomorrow or Sunday. Then it would be like a reward for getting some work done! I’ll start with some Thanksgiving art and see how much I can get done with that. Then maybe Christmas? I can only dream of getting that far. We’ll see.</p>
<p>Later… I got a sticker sheet designed for Thanksgiving. Just have the listings and photos to do before those can go live. Very happy that’s done! My Cookie character is celebrating all the holidays lately. Haha! Maybe Christmas is next.</p>
<p>I ran out of my facial moisturizer today so went to re-order and they raised the price by over $20! It was already a semi-luxurious purchase before but now I can’t justify the cost. That’s just INSANE. I’ve been using it for years and my skin loves it. I have to fall down another skincare rabbit hole to find a replacement with all the right ingredients. Ugh.</p>
<h2>📌 Summary</h2>
<ul>
<li>✅ <strong>Great sleep</strong> (8h34m)</li>
<li>⚠️ <strong>Missed habits</strong>: yoga/movement</li>
<li>✅ <strong>All tasks completed</strong></li>
<li>✨ <strong>Mood</strong>: productive and thoughtful</li>
<li>🏷️ <strong>Tags</strong>: #shop #design #stickers</li>
</ul>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>September 4, 2025</title>

    <!-- canonical id + link -->
    <id>https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/09/04/</id>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/09/04/" type="text/html" />

    <!-- dates -->
    <updated>2025-09-04T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2025-09-04T00:00:00Z</published>

    <!-- author -->
    <author><name>Judy Winsor</name></author>

    <!-- tags -->
    
      
        <category term="#work" />
      
        <category term="#fall_weather" />
      
        <category term="#reflection" />
      
    

    <!-- full HTML content -->
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <h2>Tasks</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] Work</li>
<li>[x] Mail order</li>
</ul>
<h2>Sleep</h2>
<ul>
<li>8 hr 40 min — 86% good</li>
</ul>
<h2>Habits</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] am meds</li>
<li>[x] planner fill</li>
<li>[x] self care</li>
<li>[x] shop orders</li>
<li>[x] noon meds</li>
<li>[x] no spend</li>
<li>[x] cm + h logs</li>
<li>[x] yoga/movement</li>
</ul>
<h2>Word</h2>
<p><strong>abeyance</strong> <em>(noun)</em></p>
<ul>
<li>A formal word that is almost always used in the phrase &quot;in abeyance&quot; to describe something in a temporary state of inactivity; that is, something in a state of suspension.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>The legal case is now being held in abeyance while the parties attempt to find a mutually acceptable solution.</p>
</blockquote>
<p><em>Note: If I have heard this word before I didn’t know what it meant. Love a totally new to me word of the day.</em></p>
<h2>Journal</h2>
<p>It’s a bit weird to be going back to my day job again so soon. But Labor Day makes my week weird. It doesn’t give me a day off—just pushes my work day later. Oh well. At least I was able to do all my monthly work on the 1st of the month and be done with it.</p>
<p>It’s going to be so nice and cool out today. I’m loving these extended fall weather previews so much. We had rain yesterday and I wasn’t even mad—just happy the worst of summer is over.</p>
<p>Yesterday I hoped to do some design work but I just felt braindead. No extra juice in the tank. I was disappointed but I try to listen to my body when it tells me to rest, so I just relaxed. Hopefully this weekend will be a good one for new designs!</p>
<h2>Prompt</h2>
<p><strong>Prompt 4: What’s a recent impulse you gave into with zero regrets?</strong><br>
Quite literally I got the random craving for an Oreo today. So I bought some after work and had a few after dinner. No regrets. I rarely eat Oreos anyway, so it was one of those odd things that you might as well just have fun with anyway. At least I for reasonable, non-dangerous/overly indulgent items!</p>
<hr>
<h2>📌 Summary</h2>
<ul>
<li>✅ <strong>Great sleep</strong> (8 hr 40 min)</li>
<li>✅ <strong>All habits completed</strong></li>
<li>✅ <strong>All tasks completed</strong></li>
<li>✨ <strong>Mood</strong>: reflective but optimistic</li>
<li>🏷️ <strong>Tags</strong>: #work #fall_weather #reflection</li>
</ul>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>September 3, 2025</title>

    <!-- canonical id + link -->
    <id>https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/09/03/</id>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/09/03/" type="text/html" />

    <!-- dates -->
    <updated>2025-09-03T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2025-09-03T00:00:00Z</published>

    <!-- author -->
    <author><name>Judy Winsor</name></author>

    <!-- tags -->
    
      
        <category term="#haircut" />
      
        <category term="#rainyday" />
      
        <category term="#autumnvibes" />
      
    

    <!-- full HTML content -->
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <h2>Tasks</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] HF delivery</li>
<li>[x] Haircut</li>
<li>[x] Shower</li>
</ul>
<h2>Sleep</h2>
<ul>
<li>9 hr 6 min — 86% good</li>
</ul>
<h2>Habits</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] Am meds</li>
<li>[x] Planner fill</li>
<li>[x] Self care</li>
<li>[x] Shop orders</li>
<li>[x] Noon meds</li>
<li>[x] No spend</li>
<li>[x] CM + H logs</li>
<li>[ ] Yoga/movement</li>
</ul>
<h2>Word</h2>
<p><strong>trivial</strong> <em>(adjective)</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Something of little worth or importance</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>Although her parents initially dismissed her love of pop music as a trivial matter, it became clear as she applied to colleges with strong popular music programs that much of her life was going to be dedicated to it.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2>Journal</h2>
<p>Got my hair trimmed today! It needed it. Also got a coupon for $10 off next time. I need to remember to use that! It was pouring rain right before I left the house but when I got out there, there wasn’t even a drop. Had to keep switching my windshield wipers all the way to the salon. Wacky! Oh and the Halloween store is open already! Too soon! I’m okay with autumn stuff but Halloween is still almost two months away!</p>
<p>Later: I don’t really know why but my creative brain was not functioning today. I had a big burst towards the end of August with lots of highly focused energy days, so this must be the brain’s way of rebalancing things out. Just a day to watch the second part of &quot;Wednesday&quot; on Netflix and put together a jigsaw puzzle I started yesterday. Back to work tomorrow.</p>
<h2>Prompt</h2>
<p><strong>Prompt 3: What’s the most ridiculous fall-themed product you secretly love?</strong><br>
I don’t know that I fall for any seasonal hype products… I don’t love coffee so I don’t get the pumpkin spice latte. I’m not really a seasonal food person either. I guess I kind of wanted apple cider but that’s not ridiculous or secret. I’m just not secretive with anything.</p>
<h2>📌 Summary</h2>
<ul>
<li>✅ <strong>Great sleep</strong> (9 hr 6 min)</li>
<li>⚠️ <strong>Missed habits</strong>: yoga/movement</li>
<li>✅ <strong>All tasks completed</strong></li>
<li>✨ <strong>Mood</strong>: low creative energy, leaning into rest</li>
<li>🏷️ <strong>Tags</strong>: #haircut #rainyday #autumnvibes</li>
</ul>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
