<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en-US">
  <title>Judy Winsor — Journal</title>
  <id>https://journal.judywinsor.com</id>
  <updated>2025-08-19T00:00:00Z</updated>
  <generator>Eleventy</generator>

  <!-- self + site links -->
  <link rel="self" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com/feed.atom" type="application/atom+xml" />
  <link rel="alternate" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com" type="text/html" />

  
  <entry>
    <title></title>

    <!-- canonical id + link -->
    <id>https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/08/19/</id>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/08/19/" type="text/html" />

    <!-- dates -->
    <updated>2025-08-19T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2025-08-19T00:00:00Z</published>

    <!-- author -->
    <author><name>Judy Winsor</name></author>

    <!-- tags -->
    
      
        <category term="" />
      
        <category term="" />
      
        <category term="" />
      
    

    <!-- full HTML content -->
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <h2>Tasks</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] appt. 3pm</li>
<li>[x] mail order</li>
<li>[x] list 2026 calendars</li>
</ul>
<h2>Sleep</h2>
<ul>
<li>9 hr 2 min — 83% good</li>
</ul>
<h2>Habits</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] Am meds</li>
<li>[x] Planner fill</li>
<li>[x] Self care</li>
<li>[x] Shop orders</li>
<li>[x] Noon meds</li>
<li>[x] No spend</li>
<li>[x] CM + H logs</li>
<li>[ ] Yoga/movement</li>
</ul>
<h2>Word</h2>
<p><strong>euphemism</strong> <em>(noun)</em></p>
<ul>
<li>a mild or pleasant word or phrase that is used instead of one that is unpleasant or offensive</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>The HR department advises using the euphemism &quot;let go&quot; instead of saying that someone was fired.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2>Journal</h2>
<p>I have off work this Thursday due to my dentist appointment getting rescheduled so yesterday was my only day this week. Woo! I think I'll work on a Halloween sticker sheet and get that finished this week. I got my biggest order of sticker paper yesterday. I believe this shop is going to pick up steam, so I’m increasing how much I keep in stock. Should make the busy season a little easier on me. I hope. I need to finish listing the 2026 calendars too, stalled out at the photography phase.</p>
<p><strong>Later</strong> — Okay, I took some photos and listed them on my website… only to realize I didn’t actually cut any inventory for 2 of 3 sizes. Wow brain! Whoops. So I cut some and I’ll finish the rest tomorrow. I swear I’m running on brain fumes lately. I kind of wish I could take a month off for a sort of resting vacation. I’ll do okay for a day or two, and then my energy just completely tanks out. I hope I don’t go full burnout mode. I’m trying to pace myself but doing it all alone just means stuff HAS to get done whether I have energy for it or not. Running a whole business requires a constant shifting of roles and usually that’s what makes it fun for me. But when I’m tired it just means all areas can suffer equally.</p>
<h2>📌 Summary</h2>
<ul>
<li>✅ <strong>Great sleep</strong> (9 hr 2 min)</li>
<li>⚠️ <strong>Missed habits</strong>: yoga/movement</li>
<li>✅ <strong>All tasks completed</strong></li>
<li>✨ <strong>Mood</strong>: running on brain fumes, tired but persistent</li>
<li>🏷️ <strong>Tags</strong>: #smallbusiness #dentist #stickers</li>
</ul>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title></title>

    <!-- canonical id + link -->
    <id>https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/08/18/</id>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/08/18/" type="text/html" />

    <!-- dates -->
    <updated>2025-08-18T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2025-08-18T00:00:00Z</published>

    <!-- author -->
    <author><name>Judy Winsor</name></author>

    <!-- tags -->
    
      
        <category term="" />
      
        <category term="" />
      
        <category term="" />
      
    

    <!-- full HTML content -->
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <h2>Tasks</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] workday</li>
<li>[x] mail orders</li>
</ul>
<h2>Sleep</h2>
<ul>
<li>8 hr 24 min — 84% good</li>
</ul>
<h2>Habits</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] am meds</li>
<li>[x] planner fill</li>
<li>[x] self care</li>
<li>[x] shop orders</li>
<li>[x] noon meds</li>
<li>[x] no spend</li>
<li>[x] CM + H logs</li>
<li>[x] yoga/movement</li>
</ul>
<h2>Word</h2>
<p><strong>ostentatious</strong> <em>(adj.)</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Describes someone or something that displays wealth, knowledge, power, etc. in a way that is meant to attract attention, admiration, or envy.</li>
<li>Things that tend to stand out as overly elaborate or conspicuous.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>The resort town is famous for its extravagantly expensive summer homes, which some tourists view as impressive; others deem them merely ostentatious.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2>Journal</h2>
<p>I woke up in the middle of the night and couldn’t get back to sleep for an hour. Those types of nights totally ruin my mood. I hate wondering: will I get back to sleep or will I just lay here doing nothing until morning comes? It’s probably largely because I ate a brownie after dinner. Too indulgent and my stomach said no. But when life offers you a brownie you gotta take it! lol.</p>
<p>Anyways I did take it easy yesterday but ended up with a headache anyway. I drew 3 stickers and then I told myself to stop so I could rest. I guess that was too much. Me and my body lately… can’t just get along I guess.</p>
<h2>Prompt</h2>
<p><strong>Prompt 18: What’s your go-to response when someone asks, “How’s it going?”</strong><br>
Easy? “I’m good! How are you?” Sometimes I’ll throw in something about the weather: “Sure is hot out there.” As a neurodivergent human, it’s pretty normal to script answers like this. I try to change it slightly if I know someone a little better. But often people aren’t actually curious about your life and they are just being polite — a quick answer is sufficient and even preferred to a totally honest one.</p>
<h2>📌 Summary</h2>
<ul>
<li>✅ <strong>Great sleep</strong> (8h 24m)</li>
<li>✅ <strong>All habits completed</strong></li>
<li>✅ <strong>All tasks completed</strong></li>
<li>✨ <strong>Mood</strong>: tired but reflective</li>
<li>🏷️ <strong>Tags</strong>: #sleep #reflection #prompt_response</li>
</ul>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title></title>

    <!-- canonical id + link -->
    <id>https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/08/17/</id>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/08/17/" type="text/html" />

    <!-- dates -->
    <updated>2025-08-17T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2025-08-17T00:00:00Z</published>

    <!-- author -->
    <author><name>Judy Winsor</name></author>

    <!-- tags -->
    
      
        <category term="" />
      
        <category term="" />
      
        <category term="" />
      
    

    <!-- full HTML content -->
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <h2>Tasks</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] Bath</li>
<li>[x] Weekly planning</li>
<li>[x] Refill pillboxes</li>
<li>[x] Trash day</li>
<li>[ ] Headache!</li>
</ul>
<h2>Sleep</h2>
<ul>
<li>8 hr 15 min — 86% good</li>
</ul>
<h2>Habits</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] am meds</li>
<li>[x] planner fill</li>
<li>[x] self care</li>
<li>[x] shop orders</li>
<li>[x] noon meds</li>
<li>[x] no spend</li>
<li>[x] CM + H logs</li>
<li>[ ] yoga/movement</li>
</ul>
<h2>Word</h2>
<p><strong>glitch</strong> <em>(noun)</em></p>
<ul>
<li>an informal word referring to an unexpected and usually minor problem, especially used for a minor problem with a machine or device, such as a computer.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>The email went out to everyone in the company because of a technical glitch.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Content idea: various pen tests on my sticker paper</p>
<h2>Journal</h2>
<p>Yesterday was surprisingly productive. I’m going to take it easy today. I really had 3 really focused days in a row. Which is very unusual for me. Maybe I’m getting excited because Hobonichi reveals their 2026 planners every day on social media. So I’m thinking about the future! I’ve been thinking about the end of year, fall, and the holidays too. Lots of projects and ideas percolating.</p>
<h2>Prompt</h2>
<p><strong>Prompt 17: What’s the most recent piece of advice you’ve completely ignored?</strong><br>
Kind of hard to think of any. If I feel like certain advice isn’t right for me, I think I just mentally trash it after I hear it. Otherwise I just feel guilty. I guess I heard that if you have pale skin you should really be getting your skin checked regularly with a dermatologist. I’m still planning to make an appointment but I just don’t know logistically how to make the appointment and make sure it’s covered by insurance. So I’m procrastinated because ADHD makes it feel like too many steps. So it’s advice I will eventually get to but for now it’s getting ignored.</p>
<hr>
<h2>📌 Summary</h2>
<ul>
<li>✅ <strong>Great sleep</strong></li>
<li>⚠️ <strong>Missed habits</strong>: yoga/movement</li>
<li>✅ <strong>All tasks completed</strong> (except &quot;headache!&quot; noted, not a task)</li>
<li>✨ <strong>Mood</strong>: reflective but productive</li>
<li>🏷️ <strong>Tags</strong>: #hobonichi #productivity #reflection</li>
</ul>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title></title>

    <!-- canonical id + link -->
    <id>https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/08/16/</id>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/08/16/" type="text/html" />

    <!-- dates -->
    <updated>2025-08-16T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2025-08-16T00:00:00Z</published>

    <!-- author -->
    <author><name>Judy Winsor</name></author>

    <!-- tags -->
    
      
        <category term="" />
      
        <category term="" />
      
        <category term="" />
      
    

    <!-- full HTML content -->
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <h2>Tasks</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] Laundry</li>
<li>[x] Mail orders</li>
<li>[x] 2026 test cuts</li>
<li>[x] Machine setup</li>
<li>[x] Restocking</li>
</ul>
<h2>Sleep</h2>
<ul>
<li>8 hr 15 min — 74% fair (just the right amount!)</li>
</ul>
<h2>Habits</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] Am meds</li>
<li>[x] Planner fill</li>
<li>[x] Self care</li>
<li>[x] Shop orders</li>
<li>[x] Noon meds</li>
<li>[x] No spend</li>
<li>[x] CM + H logs</li>
<li>[ ] Yoga/movement</li>
</ul>
<h2>Word</h2>
<p><strong>tempestuous</strong> <em>(adj.)</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Something that is related to or resembles a violent storm; turbulent, stormy.</li>
<li>Figuratively: someone full of strong emotions, such as anger or excitement.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p><em>On its return to port, the unlucky schooner was beset by tempestuous weather and nearly capsized.</em></p>
</blockquote>
<h2>Journal</h2>
<p>Yesterday was a good day. I hadn’t planned on designing 3 whole sticker sheets but it worked out. I’m still stuck, unable to use Adobe Illustrator when I’m cutting stickers but the calendars get started in Affinity Publisher so I could actually do design and cutting at the same time. Like I used to be able to. I really, really need a laptop so I can overcome that software glitch in the future.  It’s incredibly slowing to my whole work process. I cannot believe they haven’t fixed it yet either. I might have to figure out a stopgap workflow in Affinity Designer for awhile. I just don’t know if it has all the path tools I need like offset, simplify, smooth, etc.<br>
Very HIGH energy and productive day!</p>
<p>TCMC subscription arrived and I organized my whole sticker collection in binders. Yay!</p>
<h2>Prompt</h2>
<p><strong>Prompt 16: If you were a candle scent, what would be in your blend?</strong><br>
Well, I think I’d mostly have something sweet like vanilla. I’m generally a kind/sweet person with a big heart. Maybe some cinnamon for my neurospicy nature. I lean towards intensity when I do have emotions tho so maybe a hint of something stronger. I’m no fragrance expert. Maybe amber for the drama and some complexity.</p>
<hr>
<h2>📌 Summary</h2>
<ul>
<li>✅ <strong>Great sleep</strong> (just the right amount!)</li>
<li>⚠️ <strong>Missed habits</strong>: yoga/movement</li>
<li>✅ <strong>All tasks completed</strong></li>
<li>✨ <strong>Mood</strong>: high energy and productive</li>
<li>🏷️ <strong>Tags</strong>: #productivity #stickers #workflow</li>
</ul>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title></title>

    <!-- canonical id + link -->
    <id>https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/08/15/</id>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/08/15/" type="text/html" />

    <!-- dates -->
    <updated>2025-08-15T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2025-08-15T00:00:00Z</published>

    <!-- author -->
    <author><name>Judy Winsor</name></author>

    <!-- tags -->
    
      
        <category term="" />
      
        <category term="" />
      
        <category term="" />
      
    

    <!-- full HTML content -->
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <h2>Tasks</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] Mail orders</li>
<li>[x] Bath</li>
<li>[x] 2026 Calendars</li>
<li>[x] Pay CC bill</li>
</ul>
<h2>Sleep</h2>
<ul>
<li>9 hr — 87% good</li>
</ul>
<h2>Habits</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] am meds</li>
<li>[x] planner fill</li>
<li>[x] self care</li>
<li>[x] shop orders</li>
<li>[x] noon meds</li>
<li>[x] no spend</li>
<li>[x] cm + h logs</li>
<li>[ ] yoga/movement</li>
</ul>
<h2>Word</h2>
<p><strong>meander</strong> <em>(verb)</em></p>
<ul>
<li>to follow a winding or intricate course; that is, one with a lot of turns and curves—or to walk slowly without a specific goal, purpose, or direction</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>We spent the afternoon meandering around the seaside town.<br>
The river meanders through the canyon.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2>Journal</h2>
<p>Spent the day working on stuff for the shop. Got to work right away restocking low products. Then I was thinking about my next product and remembered I need to make 2026 calendar stickers for the Hobonichi planners. Took me awhile to remember how I did it last year so I documented the process this time in my Obsidian notes. Should be pretty quick from here on out. I’m just proofing them now and I should be able to get them listed this weekend. Yay! I still need to keep restocking lots of staple items and stuff some more envelopes for Q3 when I get a chance.</p>
<h2>Prompt</h2>
<p><strong>Prompt 15: What’s your most-used emoji, and does it fit your actual personality?</strong><br>
Mine is the blushing, smiling emoji surrounded by 3 little hearts. I think it fits me well because I do feel that way a lot. It’s like the “awww” emoji to me. I find a lot of things cute or adorable or I’m thankful in that way. I’m glad it wasn’t an LOL emoji cuz I rarely laugh that hard like that.</p>
<hr>
<h2>📌 Summary</h2>
<ul>
<li>✅ <strong>Great sleep</strong> (9 hr, 87%)</li>
<li>⚠️ <strong>Missed habits</strong>: yoga/movement</li>
<li>✅ <strong>All tasks completed</strong></li>
<li>✨ <strong>Mood</strong>: productive and thoughtful</li>
<li>🏷️ <strong>Tags</strong>: #shopwork #stickers #prompt_response</li>
</ul>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title></title>

    <!-- canonical id + link -->
    <id>https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/08/14/</id>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/08/14/" type="text/html" />

    <!-- dates -->
    <updated>2025-08-14T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2025-08-14T00:00:00Z</published>

    <!-- author -->
    <author><name>Judy Winsor</name></author>

    <!-- tags -->
    
      
        <category term="" />
      
        <category term="" />
      
        <category term="" />
      
    

    <!-- full HTML content -->
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <h2>Tasks</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] Work</li>
<li>[x] Mail order</li>
<li>[x] TCMC delivery</li>
</ul>
<h2>Sleep</h2>
<ul>
<li>9 hr 11 min — 88% good</li>
</ul>
<h2>Habits</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] Am meds</li>
<li>[x] Planner fill</li>
<li>[x] Self care</li>
<li>[x] Shop orders</li>
<li>[x] Noon meds</li>
<li>[x] No spend</li>
<li>[x] CM + H logs</li>
<li>[x] Yoga/movement</li>
</ul>
<h2>Word</h2>
<p><strong>immutable</strong> <em>(adj.)</em></p>
<ul>
<li>a formal word used to describe something that is unable to be changed</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>It is hardly an immutable fact that cats and dogs are sworn enemies; over the years our golden retriever has grown both fond and protective of her tabby housemate.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2>Journal</h2>
<p>Man my sleep has been so inconsistent lately. Very strange. Anyway, today is a work day. Next week I had to reschedule my dentist appt to Thursday because they didn’t have any other days. I also got some sticker sheets cut yesterday. Somehow I oversold by 1 so I had to restock ASAP. I’m always super diligent with my inventory tracking so I don’t know what happened. I’m gonna blame the tools. Not human error. Ha!! Probably, actually my fault somewhere. I wonder if other shop owners under list their inventory by 1–10 or something so they don’t oversell? The idea of keeping multiple versions of my inventory sounds more complicated than I want.</p>
<h2>Prompt</h2>
<p><strong>Prompt 14: If you had to eat only foods that start with one letter for the day, what letter would you choose?</strong><br>
Won’t be a very nutritious day but I’d pick M. I could have a muffin for breakfast, macaroni and cheese for dinner. I don’t know what my snacks/lunch would be tough. Uh… mozzarella string cheese? Oh I could make something mini: like a mini quiche or something. And maybe some milk chocolate or a Mr. Goodbar if I’m craving dessert. IDK this is a HARD question!</p>
<h2>📌 Summary</h2>
<ul>
<li>✅ <strong>Great sleep</strong></li>
<li>✅ <strong>All habits completed</strong></li>
<li>✅ <strong>All tasks completed</strong></li>
<li>✨ <strong>Mood</strong>: productive but puzzled about inventory</li>
<li>🏷️ <strong>Tags</strong>: #work_day #inventory_issue #tcmc_delivery</li>
</ul>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title></title>

    <!-- canonical id + link -->
    <id>https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/08/13/</id>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/08/13/" type="text/html" />

    <!-- dates -->
    <updated>2025-08-13T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2025-08-13T00:00:00Z</published>

    <!-- author -->
    <author><name>Judy Winsor</name></author>

    <!-- tags -->
    
      
        <category term="" />
      
        <category term="" />
      
        <category term="" />
      
    

    <!-- full HTML content -->
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <h2>Tasks</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] Appointment 3pm</li>
<li>[x] Mail order</li>
<li>[x] HF delivery</li>
<li>[x] Rescheduled dentist</li>
</ul>
<h2>Sleep</h2>
<ul>
<li>7 hr 20 min — 82% good</li>
</ul>
<h2>Habits</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] am meds</li>
<li>[x] planner fill</li>
<li>[x] self care</li>
<li>[x] shop orders</li>
<li>[x] noon meds</li>
<li>[x] no spend</li>
<li>[x] CM HT logs</li>
<li>[ ] yoga/movement</li>
</ul>
<h2>Word</h2>
<p><strong>calculus</strong> <em>(noun)</em></p>
<ul>
<li>an advanced branch of mathematics that deals mostly with rates of change and with finding lengths, areas, volumes.</li>
<li>also: for the act of calculating; that is, estimating something by using practical judgement, or solving/probing the meaning of something.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>By my calculus the more efficient air conditioner will have paid for itself within a span of five years.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2>Journal</h2>
<p>I'm changing my daily habit from social media post to self-care. I'm pretty burnt out on social media so it's just not going to be a daily priority for me anymore. I'd rather work directly on my business designing new products. Those will last and add value for a lot longer than anything I put on social media anyway.</p>
<p>Last night it took me hours to fall asleep. My dental cleaning got cancelled so I think I had saved up energy for that. Then it had nowhere to go. So—insomnia. Not all that surprising, but frustrating anyway. Maybe I'll cut a few sticker sheets to feel productive today, or work on my special app thing for Hobonichi planners. Not sure yet, but coding does seem to have my heart lately.</p>
<h2>Prompt</h2>
<p><strong>Prompt 13: What's your current &quot;comfort rewatch&quot; TV show, movie, or YT channel?</strong><br>
Right now I'm watching &quot;The Vampire Diaries&quot; but I don't know how far I'll get. It's not an ultimate favorite, but it reminds me of nostalgic fashion and high school drama. I watch old TCMC videos from Helen if I want something cozy and very chill. A classic rewatch is &quot;Supernatural&quot; for me. I've watched it many times!</p>
<h2>📌 Summary</h2>
<ul>
<li>⚠️ <strong>Short sleep</strong> (7h 20m)</li>
<li>⚠️ <strong>Missed habits</strong>: yoga/movement</li>
<li>✅ <strong>All tasks completed</strong></li>
<li>✨ <strong>Mood</strong>: reflective but mildly frustrated</li>
<li>🏷️ <strong>Tags</strong>: #selfcare #burnoutrecovery #productdesign</li>
</ul>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title></title>

    <!-- canonical id + link -->
    <id>https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/08/12/</id>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/08/12/" type="text/html" />

    <!-- dates -->
    <updated>2025-08-12T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2025-08-12T00:00:00Z</published>

    <!-- author -->
    <author><name>Judy Winsor</name></author>

    <!-- tags -->
    
      
        <category term="" />
      
        <category term="" />
      
        <category term="" />
      
    

    <!-- full HTML content -->
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <h2>Tasks</h2>
<ul>
<li>[ ] Dentist 2pm → cancelled</li>
<li>[x] Mail orders</li>
</ul>
<h2>Sleep</h2>
<ul>
<li>9 hr 5 min — 84% good</li>
</ul>
<h2>Habits</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] am meds</li>
<li>[x] planner fill</li>
<li>[ ] s.m. post</li>
<li>[x] shop orders</li>
<li>[x] noon meds</li>
<li>[x] no spend</li>
<li>[x] cm + h logs</li>
<li>[ ] yoga/movement</li>
</ul>
<h2>Word</h2>
<p><strong>ramshackle</strong> <em>(adj.)</em></p>
<ul>
<li>describes things that are in a very bad condition and need to be repaired, or that are carelessly or loosely constructed</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>Toward the back of the property sat a ramshackle old shed.<br>
The book had a ramshackle plot that was confusing and unbelievable.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2>Journal</h2>
<p>Ugh I have to be an adult today and take care of my body for future me. Present day me is annoyed. I know lots of people don’t like the dentist and try to be mature about it. It will just never not be weird to have someone all up in my personal space bubble like that. I just find it awkward and that’s that. My sensory system hates it. Unfortunately it will probably drain all my good creative energy for the day so I’m not planning on any big projects for the day.</p>
<p><strong>Cancelled</strong> — Well the dentist called and had to cancel because they don’t have any power. The flooding backed up more in town, and we had a windy storm last night. I guess more places lost power. What a mess.</p>
<h2>Prompt</h2>
<p><strong>Prompt 12:</strong> If you could swap lives with a fictional character for one day, who would it be?<br>
Maybe a Dr. Strange type person. If I could teleport and see a bunch of world landmarks in a day that would be so cool. And the power to control reality, yeah. I don’t love travel or sleeping in hotels so just a quick trip around the world for zero money. Seems like the best way to maximize one day of a borrowed life.</p>
<h2>📌 Summary</h2>
<ul>
<li>✅ <strong>Great sleep</strong></li>
<li>⚠️ <strong>Missed habits</strong>: sm post, yoga/movement</li>
<li>⚠️ <strong>Some tasks incomplete</strong>: Dentist cancelled</li>
<li>✨ <strong>Mood</strong>: drained but relieved</li>
<li>🏷️ <strong>Tags</strong>: #dentist #storm #flooding</li>
</ul>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title></title>

    <!-- canonical id + link -->
    <id>https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/08/11/</id>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/08/11/" type="text/html" />

    <!-- dates -->
    <updated>2025-08-11T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2025-08-11T00:00:00Z</published>

    <!-- author -->
    <author><name>Judy Winsor</name></author>

    <!-- tags -->
    
      
        <category term="" />
      
        <category term="" />
      
        <category term="" />
      
    

    <!-- full HTML content -->
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <h2>Tasks</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] Work</li>
<li>[x] Pickup Rx</li>
</ul>
<h2>Sleep</h2>
<ul>
<li>8 hr 40 min — 87% good</li>
</ul>
<h2>Habits</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] Am meds</li>
<li>[x] Planner fill</li>
<li>[ ] S.M. post</li>
<li>[x] Shop orders</li>
<li>[x] Noon meds</li>
<li>[x] No spend</li>
<li>[x] Cm + H logs</li>
<li>[x] Yoga/movement</li>
</ul>
<h2>Word</h2>
<p><strong>stipulate</strong> <em>(verb)</em></p>
<ul>
<li>to demand or require something as part of an agreement</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>The rules stipulate that players must wear uniforms.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2>Journal</h2>
<p>Phew no major rainfall last night. Just a short storm. Hopefully it didn’t make the flooding much worse. My aunt went to the Falls and apparently it stinks so bad they didn’t stop to look. How sad! And I’ve seen countless people wading into it with their kids to play. Oh the bacteria of it all. Do they not watch the news or what? M. says the lake has receded a bit overnight so that’s good. We got sooo lucky. I’m so grateful. I may have lost a little sleep but not having to gut our basement or be trapped in our neighborhood is a wonderful blessing. Hopefully none of the roads I take to work got flooded!</p>
<h2>Prompt</h2>
<p><strong>Prompt 11: What's your most irrational fear that you know is silly, but still have?</strong><br>
No origin story but I’m terrified of walking behind people fishing. I have a fear that they’ll swing back their pole to get the line out and it will instead catch on my face and hook me. It’s such a specific thing… maybe I had a nightmare like that or something. I just do NOT want to walk near anyone that’s fishing at all.</p>
<p>Much later: Let’s all just agree that Bachelor in Paradise is a ridiculous show. I don’t know why hate-watching something feels so cathartic though?</p>
<h2>📌 Summary</h2>
<ul>
<li>✅ <strong>Great sleep</strong></li>
<li>⚠️ <strong>Missed habits</strong>: sm_post</li>
<li>✅ <strong>All tasks completed</strong></li>
<li>✨ <strong>Mood</strong>: relieved and grateful</li>
<li>🏷️ <strong>Tags</strong>: #flooding #workday #irrational_fear</li>
</ul>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title></title>

    <!-- canonical id + link -->
    <id>https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/08/10/</id>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/08/10/" type="text/html" />

    <!-- dates -->
    <updated>2025-08-10T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2025-08-10T00:00:00Z</published>

    <!-- author -->
    <author><name>Judy Winsor</name></author>

    <!-- tags -->
    
      
        <category term="" />
      
        <category term="" />
      
        <category term="" />
      
    

    <!-- full HTML content -->
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <h2>Tasks</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] Weekly planning</li>
<li>[x] Refill pillboxes</li>
<li>[x] Bath</li>
<li>[x] Trash day</li>
</ul>
<h2>Sleep</h2>
<ul>
<li>6 hr 59 min — 78% fair</li>
</ul>
<h2>Habits</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] Am meds</li>
<li>[x] Planner fill</li>
<li>[ ] S.M. post</li>
<li>[x] Shop orders</li>
<li>[x] Noon meds</li>
<li>[x] No spend</li>
<li>[x] Cm &amp; H logs</li>
<li>[x] Yoga/movement</li>
</ul>
<h2>Word</h2>
<p><strong>hidebound</strong> <em>(adj.)</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Someone or something that is inflexible and unwilling to accept new or different ideas.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>Although somewhat stuffy and strict, the professor did not so completely adhere to hidebound academic tradition that he wouldn’t teach class outside on a especially lovely day.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2>Journal</h2>
<p>Wow last night we got over 10 inches of rain. The thunder was so loud I couldn’t fall asleep. Then around 3 a.m. our basement water alarms went off. Went to check it out and the sump pump was full. There was water leaking in from the walls and up from a crack in the floor (that I don’t think was there before). I’ve never seen anything like it. There wasn’t much to do. We turned the sump pump off and on again and it started to work again. So it was hard to settle down for sleep after that but I eventually did! Our rivers are like 2 feet higher than ever in recorded history. I’m so glad it didn’t get worse in our basement! Lots of power outages but we kept ours. I’m sure the basement would have totally flooded without the sump pump. I wonder how our neighbors did?</p>
<h2>Prompt</h2>
<p><strong>Prompt 10: If your day today was a playlist, what would be the first 3 songs?</strong></p>
<ol>
<li>Set Fire to the Rain — Adele</li>
<li>Dog Days Are Over — Florence + the Machine</li>
<li>Up All Night — Owl City (’Cuz floods and rain and I’m tired.)</li>
</ol>
<h2>📌 Summary</h2>
<ul>
<li>⚠️ <strong>Short sleep</strong></li>
<li>⚠️ <strong>Missed habits</strong>: sm_post</li>
<li>✅ <strong>All tasks completed</strong></li>
<li>✨ <strong>Mood</strong>: tired but relieved</li>
<li>🏷️ <strong>Tags</strong>: #flooding #home #storm</li>
</ul>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title></title>

    <!-- canonical id + link -->
    <id>https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/08/09/</id>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/08/09/" type="text/html" />

    <!-- dates -->
    <updated>2025-08-09T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2025-08-09T00:00:00Z</published>

    <!-- author -->
    <author><name>Judy Winsor</name></author>

    <!-- tags -->
    
      
        <category term="" />
      
        <category term="" />
      
        <category term="" />
      
    

    <!-- full HTML content -->
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <h2>Tasks</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] laundry</li>
<li>[x] new app dev</li>
<li>[x] TCMC B-day sale</li>
</ul>
<h2>Sleep</h2>
<ul>
<li>8 hr 14 min — 78% fair</li>
</ul>
<h2>Habits</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] am meds</li>
<li>[x] planner fill</li>
<li>[ ] s.m. post</li>
<li>[x] shop orders</li>
<li>[x] noon meds</li>
<li>[ ] no spend</li>
<li>[x] CM + H logs</li>
<li>[ ] yoga/movement</li>
</ul>
<h2>Word</h2>
<p><strong>behemoth</strong> <em>(noun)</em></p>
<ul>
<li>something of monstrous size, power, or appearance</li>
<li>biblical: a mighty animal described in the book of Job</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>The town will be voting on whether or not to let the retail behemoth build a store on the proposed site.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2>Journal</h2>
<p>Backfill: I spent the whole day on a new project. I finally figured out an easy workflow. I put the code on GitHub as a repository and then open the code space to edit the code. From there I use a Live Server extension to test all my changes — quick and easy in another browser window. I can even use my iPad, which is mainly what I use daily anywhere. I made lots of progress and figured out how to commit changes to Git as I went. I’m creating a super fun tool for anyone who wants to track their weather in a planner or journal.</p>
<p>I’m doing most of the code in JavaScript, which I’m honestly not super familiar with, but this project isn’t super complex — it’s layout heavy. So it’s fun to learn as I go. The more I change, the more I understand it. I’m thinking I can make a few of the styles available free, then maybe add a one-time paid upgrade to unlock more themes and options. IDK — I’ve never sold a code project like this before. I’ve made tools for myself, but if it breaks I can either abandon it or try to fix it. IDK if I’d be all that helpful in a “tech support” scenario. I’ll just wait and see how I feel once it’s finished.</p>
<h2>📌 Summary</h2>
<ul>
<li>⚠️ <strong>Short sleep</strong> (under 8h15m)</li>
<li>⚠️ <strong>Missed habits</strong>: sm_post, no_spend, yoga/movement</li>
<li>✅ <strong>All tasks completed</strong></li>
<li>✨ <strong>Mood</strong>: productive and focused</li>
<li>🏷️ <strong>Tags</strong>: #coding #journal #weather-tracking</li>
</ul>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title></title>

    <!-- canonical id + link -->
    <id>https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/08/08/</id>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/08/08/" type="text/html" />

    <!-- dates -->
    <updated>2025-08-08T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2025-08-08T00:00:00Z</published>

    <!-- author -->
    <author><name>Judy Winsor</name></author>

    <!-- tags -->
    
      
        <category term="" />
      
        <category term="" />
      
        <category term="" />
      
        <category term="" />
      
    

    <!-- full HTML content -->
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <h2>Tasks</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] Bath</li>
<li>[x] Mail orders</li>
</ul>
<h2>Sleep</h2>
<ul>
<li>8 hr 23 min — 84% good</li>
</ul>
<h2>Habits</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] am meds</li>
<li>[x] planner fill</li>
<li>[ ] S.M. Post</li>
<li>[x] shop orders</li>
<li>[x] noon meds</li>
<li>[x] no spend</li>
<li>[x] CM+H logs</li>
<li>[ ] yoga/movement</li>
</ul>
<h2>Word</h2>
<p><strong>winsome</strong> <em>(adjective)</em></p>
<ul>
<li>describes people + things that are cheerful, pleasant, and appealing</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>Though a relative newcomer to acting, Maya won the casting directors over with her winsome charm, which was perfect for the role of a plucky young superhero.<br>
Our winsome guide put us at ease immediately.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2>Journal</h2>
<p>I had a terrible time trying to fall asleep last night. I just couldn’t relax. IDK if it’s dental appt anxiety or what, but that isn’t until next week. Terribly annoying. So I started today with a super relaxing bath. Just want to wash away the bad vibes. I think I’ll take it kind of slow today. Might do some fun coding but nothing super taxing. I just don’t have a lot of extra mental resources right now. Plus I’ve already released 2 new sticker sheets so far this month. That’s quite good for me!</p>
<p>Later: I got a terrible headache so the rest of the day was mostly a wash. I was trying to teach myself more code stuff. Then me and M. decided to go out for dinner and I realized my head hurt. It didn’t get worse though so I’m surviving… just tired I guess. Yuck.</p>
<h2>Prompt</h2>
<p><strong>Prompt 8:</strong> If you could rename one everyday object to something sillier, what would you call it?<br>
Like calling a fork a “dinglehopper” in <em>The Little Mermaid</em>. Well I recently used a “gentle” exfoliator and think a better name might be Pain Paste. (It was shockingly aggressive.)</p>
<h2>📌 Summary</h2>
<ul>
<li>✅ <strong>Great sleep</strong></li>
<li>⚠️ <strong>Missed habits</strong>: sm_post, yoga_movement</li>
<li>✅ <strong>All tasks completed</strong></li>
<li>✨ <strong>Mood</strong>: tired but mildly productive</li>
<li>🏷️ <strong>Tags</strong>: #journaling #daily_log #planner #headache</li>
</ul>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title></title>

    <!-- canonical id + link -->
    <id>https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/08/07/</id>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/08/07/" type="text/html" />

    <!-- dates -->
    <updated>2025-08-07T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2025-08-07T00:00:00Z</published>

    <!-- author -->
    <author><name>Judy Winsor</name></author>

    <!-- tags -->
    
      
        <category term="" />
      
        <category term="" />
      
        <category term="" />
      
    

    <!-- full HTML content -->
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <h2>Tasks</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] work</li>
<li>[x] mail order</li>
</ul>
<h2>Sleep</h2>
<ul>
<li>8 hr 50 min — 82% good</li>
</ul>
<h2>Habits</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] am meds</li>
<li>[x] planner fill</li>
<li>[ ] s.m. post</li>
<li>[x] shop orders</li>
<li>[x] noon meds</li>
<li>[x] no spend</li>
<li>[x] CM + H logs</li>
<li>[x] yoga/movement</li>
</ul>
<h2>Word</h2>
<p><strong>adjudicate</strong> <em>(verb)</em></p>
<ul>
<li>to make an official decision about who is right in (a dispute)</li>
<li>to act as a judge</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p><em>The case will be adjudicated in the state courts.</em><br>
<em>The property title cannot be transferred until a case concerning the affected rights of way is adjudicated.</em></p>
</blockquote>
<h2>Journal</h2>
<p>Yesterday was surprisingly productive. I designed, printed, and cut a whole new sticker sheet. Whoa! I eventually found the missing Apple Pencil and was inspired to make a sheet about clutter and disorganization. I love it! I just need to take product photos and then it can go live. Might be one of my fastest sheets ever with fresh artwork. Nothing is more inspiring than actual lived experience for me. I can feel if the message is being conveyed properly in my bones, I gotta remember to use that more often. It just feels good to process life through art that way. Like my life has more meaning than just something I experience alone.</p>
<h2>Prompt</h2>
<p><strong>Prompt 7: What's your personal &quot;comfy clothes&quot; uniform?</strong><br>
I never understood this growing up — it felt like all clothes were the same comfort (except for tight jeans). Then I grew up, gained a little weight. Man, everything digs and pulls and feels weird! If I can go a whole day with no bra (or light bralette), pajama shirt, and sweatpants, I'm very happy. I always take off my “outside clothes” first thing when I'm home for the day now. It's sooo much better. Jeans are the worst.</p>
<h2>📌 Summary</h2>
<ul>
<li>✅ <strong>Great sleep</strong></li>
<li>⚠️ <strong>Missed habits</strong>: sm post</li>
<li>✅ <strong>All tasks completed</strong></li>
<li>✨ <strong>Mood</strong>: inspired and productive</li>
<li>🏷️ <strong>Tags</strong>: #productivity #creative #planner_shop</li>
</ul>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title></title>

    <!-- canonical id + link -->
    <id>https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/08/06/</id>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/08/06/" type="text/html" />

    <!-- dates -->
    <updated>2025-08-06T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2025-08-06T00:00:00Z</published>

    <!-- author -->
    <author><name>Judy Winsor</name></author>

    <!-- tags -->
    
      
        <category term="" />
      
        <category term="" />
      
        <category term="" />
      
    

    <!-- full HTML content -->
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <h2>Tasks</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] HF delivery</li>
<li>[x] mail order</li>
<li>[ ] s.m. post → moved to 2025-08-07</li>
<li>[x] bath</li>
</ul>
<h2>Sleep</h2>
<ul>
<li>8 hr 30 min, 87% good</li>
</ul>
<h2>Habits</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] am meds</li>
<li>[x] planner fill</li>
<li>[ ] sm. post</li>
<li>[x] shop orders</li>
<li>[x] noon meds</li>
<li>[x] no spend</li>
<li>[x] CM + H logs</li>
<li>[ ] yoga/movement</li>
</ul>
<h2>Word</h2>
<p><strong>largesse</strong> <em>(noun)</em></p>
<ul>
<li>A somewhat formal word that refers to the act of giving away money or the generosity of a person who gives away money</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p><em>The community has benefited greatly from the largesse of its wealthiest family.</em><br>
<em>The local business owner is a philanthropist known for his largesse.</em></p>
</blockquote>
<h2>Journal</h2>
<p>I lost my Apple Pencil again and I can’t find it anywhere. I really wish the Magic Keyboard case had a secure spot for it. The magnet is totally unreliable. And it always hides once it falls off. It’s never just on the floor near the iPad or anything easy like that. And I don’t have the version with Find My device detection either.<br>
Plus I just have zero storage space to organize all my stuff. So that makes the search a lot more frustrating and difficult. Running a stationery shop out of your bedroom is NOT ideal.</p>
<h2>Prompt</h2>
<p><strong>Prompt 6: When was the last time you laughed so hard you couldn’t breathe?</strong><br>
Well I can remember a recent cry and laugh combo. I was talking about how I struggle to say yes to new things and new people. And they said “Your brain runs on binding contracts. Yes = now I’ve agreed to coffee every month until one of us dies.” It sounds so silly and ridiculous but it resonated so hard that I just cried and laughed about the weirdness that is my brain. Like that’s obviously ridiculous… a yes does not equal a lifetime contract, but for some reason that’s what I think.</p>
<h2>📌 Summary</h2>
<ul>
<li>✅ <strong>Great sleep</strong> (8 hr 30 min)</li>
<li>⚠️ <strong>Missed habits</strong>: sm_post, yoga/movement</li>
<li>⚠️ <strong>One task incomplete</strong></li>
<li>✨ <strong>Mood</strong>: frustrated and scattered</li>
<li>🏷️ <strong>Tags</strong>: #lostthings #stationeryshop #overwhelm</li>
</ul>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title></title>

    <!-- canonical id + link -->
    <id>https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/08/05/</id>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/08/05/" type="text/html" />

    <!-- dates -->
    <updated>2025-08-05T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2025-08-05T00:00:00Z</published>

    <!-- author -->
    <author><name>Judy Winsor</name></author>

    <!-- tags -->
    
      
        <category term="" />
      
        <category term="" />
      
        <category term="" />
      
    

    <!-- full HTML content -->
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <h2>Tasks</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] mail order</li>
</ul>
<h2>Sleep</h2>
<ul>
<li>8 hr 23 min, 84% good</li>
</ul>
<h2>Habits</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] am meds</li>
<li>[x] planner fill</li>
<li>[ ] sm post</li>
<li>[x] shop orders</li>
<li>[x] noon meds</li>
<li>[x] no spend</li>
<li>[x] cm + h logs</li>
<li>[ ] yoga/movement</li>
</ul>
<h2>Word</h2>
<p><strong>Contentious</strong> <em>(adj.)</em></p>
<ul>
<li>describing something that is likely to cause people to argue or disagree or that involves a lot of arguing.</li>
<li>For a person: someone likely or willing to argue</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>I think it's wise to avoid such a contentious topic at a dinner party.<br>
The dispute involves one of the region's most contentious leaders.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2>Journal</h2>
<p>Had a bit of an emotional day yesterday. Someone I used to work with came into work and told me some news, which wasn't a big deal in itself. It was just on the 40 min drive home while my mind wandered. I was just comparing my life and wondering why mine was so different… wondering if I missed my chances… wondering why some things just don't work out how you hope they would… and so on. Just feeling overwhelmed by emotions in general. I think I just needed a good cry to reset and get it out. I know comparison is pointless and unhelpful. It just snuck up on me. I am still grieving various things and sometimes you just gotta get it out. I think I feel better today. I think I handled the emotions well and processed some stuff that was building up. Key takeaway: It's okay to feel old negative thoughts, but then be sure to let them go. You can't just DENY them away because you're &quot;not supposed&quot; to think them. Negative stuff just happens. Old brain programming doesn't just disappear overnight. Feel it, then reframe it and move on. I think sometimes you hear advice like &quot;comparison is the thief of joy,&quot; so then maybe you feel guilty when you accidentally compare yourself to others. But that's not helpful either. It's okay, and you can get through it.</p>
<h2>Prompt</h2>
<p><strong>No prompt recorded</strong></p>
<h2>📌 Summary</h2>
<ul>
<li>✅ <strong>Great sleep</strong></li>
<li>⚠️ <strong>Missed habits</strong>: sm post, yoga/movement</li>
<li>✅ <strong>All tasks completed</strong></li>
<li>✨ <strong>Mood</strong>: reflective</li>
<li>🏷️ <strong>Tags</strong>: #reflection #mental_health #journaling</li>
</ul>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title></title>

    <!-- canonical id + link -->
    <id>https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/08/04/</id>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/08/04/" type="text/html" />

    <!-- dates -->
    <updated>2025-08-04T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2025-08-04T00:00:00Z</published>

    <!-- author -->
    <author><name>Judy Winsor</name></author>

    <!-- tags -->
    
      
        <category term="" />
      
        <category term="" />
      
        <category term="" />
      
    

    <!-- full HTML content -->
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <h2>Tasks</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] Workday</li>
<li>[x] Mail order</li>
</ul>
<h2>Sleep</h2>
<ul>
<li>8 hr 27 min — 86% good</li>
</ul>
<h2>Habits</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] am meds</li>
<li>[x] planner fill</li>
<li>[ ] s.m. post</li>
<li>[x] shop orders</li>
<li>[x] noon meds</li>
<li>[x] no spend</li>
<li>[x] cm + h logs</li>
<li>[x] yoga/movement</li>
</ul>
<h2>Word</h2>
<p><strong>tapestry</strong> <em>(noun)</em></p>
<ul>
<li>A heavy textile characterized by complicated pictorial designs and used for hangings, curtains, and upholstery. Figurative use: refers to anything made up of different things (people, colors, etc.).</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>The walls were adorned with handwoven tapestries.<br>
They enjoyed the rich tapestry of life in the city.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2>Journal</h2>
<p>Back to normal life today. Not getting too many boxes at work though so no major stress. Just the normal stress. My stomach was giving me some trouble last night. Not really sure why. I guess the pasta primavera was too creamy? Annoying. We are down to 2 episodes of <em>The Sandman</em> on Netflix. Not sure what else is left. This last episode felt like a finale.</p>
<p>Oh I got tags to work on my 11ty site. That’s fun. It’s all a bit harder than I want it to be but then it wouldn’t feel quite as good when I finally figure something out. IDK what my final goal is with the project but it’s pretty fun (usually) to just play around with the layout and design for now. Plus it's a way to go back to any day in my planner even if I don’t have it sitting in front of me.</p>
<h2>Prompt</h2>
<p><strong>What’s a small hill you’re absolutely willing to die on?</strong><br>
Baths are better than showers. They take longer BUT shouldn’t resetting your body for a new day be a little more indulgent? Enjoyable? Peaceful? Relaxing? I can’t even hear my music in a shower. Plus I just don’t feel as deeply clean. Showers work in a pinch or a rush. But the full bath is where the real body reset happens.</p>
<h2>📌 Summary</h2>
<ul>
<li>✅ <strong>Great sleep</strong></li>
<li>⚠️ <strong>Missed habits</strong>: sm_post</li>
<li>✅ <strong>All tasks completed</strong></li>
<li>✨ <strong>Mood</strong>: Normal workday stress, slight stomach upset</li>
<li>🏷️ <strong>Tags</strong>: #work #planning #selfcare</li>
</ul>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title></title>

    <!-- canonical id + link -->
    <id>https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/08/03/</id>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/08/03/" type="text/html" />

    <!-- dates -->
    <updated>2025-08-03T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2025-08-03T00:00:00Z</published>

    <!-- author -->
    <author><name>Judy Winsor</name></author>

    <!-- tags -->
    
      
        <category term="" />
      
        <category term="" />
      
        <category term="" />
      
    

    <!-- full HTML content -->
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <h2>Tasks</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] Refill pillboxes</li>
<li>[x] Weekly planning</li>
<li>[x] Trash day</li>
<li>[x] Bath</li>
<li>[x] FWP ink post</li>
</ul>
<h2>Sleep</h2>
<ul>
<li>7 hr 29 min — 80% good</li>
</ul>
<h2>Habits</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] Am meds</li>
<li>[x] Planner fill</li>
<li>[x] S.m. post</li>
<li>[x] Shop orders</li>
<li>[x] Noon meds</li>
<li>[x] No spend</li>
<li>[x] Cm + h logs</li>
<li>[ ] Yoga/movement</li>
</ul>
<h2>Word</h2>
<p><strong>egregious</strong> <em>(adj.)</em></p>
<ul>
<li>A formal word used to describe things that are conspicuously bad.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>Leaving a cellphone on during a performance is an egregious breach of theater etiquette.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2>Journal</h2>
<p>M comes back from visiting J today. Yay! Back to normal. I ended up finishing my Annual Holidays sticker sheets yesterday. I even got them listed. But by dinner my brain was melted and I struggled a lot to make myself food. So a productive day followed by a crash. I guess that makes sense even if I find it very annoying.<br>
Today is just a personal prep day. Not gonna do any shop work. I’m listening to my body and it was shouting for rest.</p>
<p>M. came back! All's right with the world. I missed her a lot this time. My whole routine felt a bit off and weird. I couldn't figure out quite how to spend my evenings. I watched some totally random movies I don’t even remember now. She's like my anchor. Even when my ADHD wants me to go wild I stick to more of a schedule when she's around. It's just easier to relax and unwind too. I had a really hard time falling asleep both nights she was gone. All is well for now though. Phew! I could use a little more shut eye tonight- back to work tomorrow.</p>
<h2>Prompt</h2>
<p><strong>Prompt 3: What’s the weirdest snack combo you genuinely enjoy?</strong><br>
I’m not sure I eat any weird combos. I like my food simple. I’m not an adventurous food person. Usually if someone finds a choice I make weird, it’s because it’s very bland. Like no ketchup or anything on fries or a hot dog. IDK, I’m not big on condiments.</p>
<hr>
<h2>📌 Summary</h2>
<ul>
<li>⚠️ <strong>Short sleep</strong></li>
<li>⚠️ <strong>Missed habits</strong>: yoga/movement</li>
<li>✅ <strong>All tasks completed</strong></li>
<li>✨ <strong>Mood</strong>: tired but content</li>
<li>🏷️ <strong>Tags</strong>: #daily #journal #reflection</li>
</ul>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title></title>

    <!-- canonical id + link -->
    <id>https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/08/02/</id>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/08/02/" type="text/html" />

    <!-- dates -->
    <updated>2025-08-02T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2025-08-02T00:00:00Z</published>

    <!-- author -->
    <author><name>Judy Winsor</name></author>

    <!-- tags -->
    
      
        <category term="" />
      
        <category term="" />
      
        <category term="" />
      
    

    <!-- full HTML content -->
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <h2>Tasks</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] Laundry</li>
<li>[x] Accounting</li>
<li>[x] Test cut</li>
<li>[x] Add inventory</li>
<li>[x] Fill fountain pen</li>
</ul>
<h2>Sleep</h2>
<ul>
<li>8 hr 57 min — 86% good</li>
</ul>
<h2>Habits</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] am meds</li>
<li>[x] planner fill</li>
<li>[ ] sm. post</li>
<li>[x] shop orders</li>
<li>[x] noon meds</li>
<li>[x] no spend</li>
<li>[x] CM + H logs</li>
<li>[ ] yoga/movement</li>
</ul>
<h2>Word</h2>
<p><strong>palimpsest</strong> <em>(noun)</em></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>original use</strong>: refers to writing material used one or more times after earlier writing has been erased; the underlying text is &quot;in palimpsest&quot;</li>
<li><strong>extended use</strong>: refers to something that has usually diverse layers or aspects apparent beneath the surface</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>Scholars believe the motive for making palimpsests was often economic — reusing parchment was cheaper than preparing a new skin.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2>Journal</h2>
<p>The Hobonichi theme for 2026 is “You Love You”! ☺️ Well, do you? I can’t wait to see what covers and visual themes they have. Even though I’ll probably just keep my same A5 Avec that I did this year. And I splurged on my cover by POTR so it would be wise to use it again unless they release the best design ever.</p>
<p>My lungs are tired from the low air quality yesterday. My Fitbit says my SpO2 overnight was 91% even though I didn’t do anything strenuous. I feel okay though. My mind is a lot clearer. I’ve already cut half of the holiday stickers and done the accounting.</p>
<p>I’ll only do a little more shop work then try to wrap it up. Maybe do some social media stuff.</p>
<h2>Prompt</h2>
<p><strong>Prompt 2: If you had to give your current mood a weather report, what would it be?</strong><br>
Maybe partly cloudy, comfortable temps with an early sunset. Haha! Does that make sense? I’m a tiny bit tired thus a few clouds. But otherwise comfortable — no big stressors currently. And since it’s the weekend I’ll wrap things up early with “sunset.” Overall pretty good!</p>
<h2>📌 Summary</h2>
<ul>
<li>✅ <strong>Great sleep</strong></li>
<li>⚠️ <strong>Missed habits</strong>: sm post, yoga/movement</li>
<li>✅ <strong>All tasks completed</strong></li>
<li>✨ <strong>Mood</strong>: comfortable but a little tired</li>
<li>🏷️ <strong>Tags</strong>: #planning #hobonichi #low_air_quality</li>
</ul>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title></title>

    <!-- canonical id + link -->
    <id>https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/08/01/</id>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/08/01/" type="text/html" />

    <!-- dates -->
    <updated>2025-08-01T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2025-08-01T00:00:00Z</published>

    <!-- author -->
    <author><name>Judy Winsor</name></author>

    <!-- tags -->
    
      
        <category term="" />
      
        <category term="" />
      
        <category term="" />
      
    

    <!-- full HTML content -->
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <h2>Tasks</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] mail order</li>
<li>[x] Beach!</li>
<li>[x] shower</li>
<li>[x] m. gone to J.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Sleep</h2>
<ul>
<li>8 hr 57 min — 83% good</li>
</ul>
<h2>Habits</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] am meds</li>
<li>[x] planner fill</li>
<li>[x] sm. post</li>
<li>[x] shop orders</li>
<li>[x] noon meds</li>
<li>[x] no spend</li>
<li>[x] CM + H logs</li>
<li>[x] yoga/movement</li>
</ul>
<h2>Word</h2>
<p><strong>dissociate</strong> <em>(verb)</em></p>
<ul>
<li>to separate oneself from association or union with someone or something</li>
<li><em>(Psychology)</em>: mentally detaching from one’s physical or emotional experiences</li>
<li><em>(Chemistry)</em>: to separate a chemical compound into its constituent parts, especially through the application of heat or a solvent</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>The director has tried to dissociate herself from her earlier films.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2>Journal</h2>
<p>Finally a free day with super nice weather! Ah! Yay! It had been too long. I went to my favorite beach for guaranteed fun and rocks to look at. The waves were big-ish but the absolute perfect temperature. The breeze was perfect. I didn’t notice the air quality feeling smokey either. You could see it if you looked far enough away though. Lots of people there and a few other rock hunters. Nothing spectacular found but I did get a piece of sea glass… my 2nd or 3rd piece ever. Just clear in color but still exciting to me anyway. I feel so relieved I finally got some sun and air.</p>
<img src="/images/IMG_5060.jpeg" alt="The Beach by Lake Michigan"  style="max-width:280px;height:auto;">
<p>Oh! I saw 4 sandhill cranes today and a deer. The other day after work I saw a mom and baby deer cross the road. So cute!</p>
<h2>Prompt</h2>
<p><strong>Prompt 1: What’s the last app you opened on your phone and why?</strong><br>
Well before Safari—to get this prompt from my website—I think it was Messages to read a text from my mom. We were just talking about some random stuff to buy from Target. Thrilling!</p>
<hr>
<h2>📌 Summary</h2>
<ul>
<li>✅ <strong>Great sleep</strong></li>
<li>✅ <strong>All habits completed</strong></li>
<li>✅ <strong>All tasks completed</strong></li>
<li>✨ <strong>Mood</strong>: relieved and happy</li>
<li>🏷️ <strong>Tags</strong>: #beach #sunnyday #seaglass</li>
</ul>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title></title>

    <!-- canonical id + link -->
    <id>https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/07/31/</id>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://journal.judywinsor.com/journal/2025/07/31/" type="text/html" />

    <!-- dates -->
    <updated>2025-07-31T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <published>2025-07-31T00:00:00Z</published>

    <!-- author -->
    <author><name>Judy Winsor</name></author>

    <!-- tags -->
    
      
        <category term="" />
      
        <category term="" />
      
        <category term="" />
      
    

    <!-- full HTML content -->
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
      <h2>Tasks</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] Workday</li>
</ul>
<h2>Sleep</h2>
<ul>
<li>8 hr 11 min — 85% good</li>
</ul>
<h2>Habits</h2>
<ul>
<li>[x] Am meds</li>
<li>[x] Planner fill</li>
<li>[x] Sm post</li>
<li>[x] Shop orders</li>
<li>[x] Noon meds</li>
<li>[x] No spend</li>
<li>[x] Cm + H logs</li>
<li>[x] Yoga/movement</li>
</ul>
<h2>Word</h2>
<p><strong>petulant</strong> <em>(adjective)</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Describes a person who is angry and annoyed, or an attitude or behaviour showing the emotions of such a person.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>I didn’t appreciate being accused of acting like a petulant toddler.<br>
Her tone became petulant when she realized that items on sale were no longer available.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2>Journal</h2>
<p>Last work day of the month. I feel like July was both fast and slow. I hated all the heat and humidity. I just stayed inside the whole month. It was miserable. We had one or two good days and I was busy with work for both. No idea what August will hold but it’s typically a hot and humid one too. This whole weekend should be way nicer though so I’m gonna go to a beach at least once. I’m going stir crazy inside.</p>
<p>I spent all day yesterday comparing my Eleventy site to my Grow site. I’m not sure which I like better. Cloudflare kept injecting extra code into my 11ty site and breaking the footer. So I turned it off for that subdomain. But I do hate the manual FTP process. Maybe I need different software? It’s just slow for even tiny files. Maybe I should FTP right from VS Code itself instead of using Forklift? Apparently my hosting isn’t compatible with the more modern tools (like GitHub) so it just slows everything down. Maybe I should consider switching hosting companies? This one’s affordable and I’ve used them forever. Migrating servers always becomes a nightmare. All the databases and DNS and subdomains and emails and all the custom rules and logins. It always sucks…</p>
<h2>📌 Summary</h2>
<ul>
<li>⚠️ <strong>Short sleep</strong> (8 hr 11 min)</li>
<li>✅ <strong>All habits completed</strong></li>
<li>✅ <strong>All tasks completed</strong></li>
<li>✨ <strong>Mood</strong>: Stuck inside but reflective</li>
<li>🏷️ <strong>Tags</strong>: #journal #daily #no_missed_habits</li>
</ul>

    ]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
